【music】
【音楽】
good welcome
ようこそ
Thank you for participating in this month's quiz
今月のクイズにご参加いただきありがとうございました
Today our leader is
今日の私たちのリーダーは、
Researcher Zhao Guangyu
研究者 趙光宇
Is a researcher at the Institute of Employment and Life Support
雇用・生活支援機構研究員
Dr. Zhao is a member of the National Central University Job Research Institute
Zhao 博士は、国立センター大学雇用研究所のメンバーです。
Graduate Master
修士課程
PhD
博士
Zhuo Shi
卓史
Sui Shi and Zhuo Shi are there
隋石と卓石がいる
Then go to the Union Campus of the University of California
その後、カリフォルニア大学のユニオンキャンパスへ行きます。
This is the Riverside campus
ここはリバーサイドキャンパスです
Dr. Duke Read
念公督博士
Got a doctorate degree in occupational science there
そこで作業科学の博士号を取得
Washington State University
ワシントン州立大学
it's seattle
シアトルです
Bouman does Postal
ボウマンは郵便を行う
Then
それから
in molecular biology
分子生物学で
Should be biochemistry
生化学のはず
During this process, I have always been interested in the study of plants
その過程で、私はずっと植物の研究に興味を持っていました。
Returned to Zhongyuan Hospital in 1999
1999年に中原病院に戻った。
Joined the Phytomachine Microbiology Institute team
ファイトマシン微生物研究所チームに参加
it is now a researcher at the institute
彼は今、研究所の研究者です
And the deputy director
そして副院長は
director here
ここのディレクター
yes we are
はい、私たちはそうです
The Botanical Sanitation Institute belongs to the Central Plains
植物衛生研究所はセントラルプレーンズに属します
In the life sciences, it is the first
生命科学の分野では初めてです。
Yes, the land here used to be the land of the Botanical Guard
そう、ここの土地はかつて植物警備隊の土地だったのだ
our side too
私たちの側も
Later, it was given to us by us, it seems like this
後日、私達から頂きました、こんな感じです
right
右
So its research work in plant reproduction
植物の生殖における研究活動です
There are many studies on the process of growth
成長過程については多くの研究がなされている
have very good grades
とても良い成績を持っています
Today he will share with us
今日、彼は私たちと分かち合います
It is using genetic technology
遺伝子技術を使っているんですね
To understand the growth process of plants
植物の成長過程を理解する
OK, then we welcome Dr. Zhao Guangyu
OK、では趙光宇博士を歓迎します。
Thank you, Vice President Liu, for your introduction
劉副社長、ご紹介いただきありがとうございます。
first of all i want to thank you
まず最初に感謝したいです
I would also like to thank the secretary of the headquarters for giving me this opportunity
このような機会を与えてくださった本社秘書にも感謝したいと思います。
Let me share with you the past period of time that we have
私たちがこれまで過ごしてきた期間を皆さんと共有しましょう
in botany
植物学で
Especially the research on the reproductive growth of plants
特に植物の生殖成長に関する研究
More importantly, thank you all for coming today
それよりも大切なのは、今日は来てくれてありがとう
i know tonight
今夜は知っています
You're probably all going to class
皆さんもきっと授業に通っているでしょう
come back later
後で戻ってきます
I try to keep this content from being too old
このコンテンツが古くなりすぎないように努めています
So this time we start today
ということで今回は今日からスタートです
Basically, our laboratory mainly does
基本的に当研究室では主に以下のことを行っています。
reproductive growth of plants
植物の生殖成長
And that's what I've always been interested in
そして、それは私がいつも興味を持っていたことです
Before we introduce plant reproductive growth
植物の生殖成長を導入する前に
Let me introduce you first
まずはご紹介させていただきます
There is a typical plant cell
典型的な植物細胞があります
plant cells and animal cells
植物細胞と動物細胞
The biggest difference is
最大の違いは
it has leaves
葉があります
it has cell arms
セルアームがある
and most importantly
最も重要な
it has a large cell in the middle
真ん中に大きなセルがある
vacuoles of cells
細胞の液胞
In addition there are many
この他にもたくさんあります
protoplasmic contact wire
原形質コンタクトワイヤー
So this plant cell
つまりこの植物細胞は
Can communicate with another plant cell
他の植物細胞と通信できる
Through this protoplasmic connecting thread
この原形質接続糸を通して
They can directly communicate with each other
お互いに直接通信できる
The structure of the whole plant cell
植物細胞全体の構造
We can learn from molecules, loads, entrained gas
分子、荷重、同伴ガスから学ぶことができる
cells all the way up to the whole plant
細胞から植物全体まで
leaf filter
リーフフィルター
They end up forming leaf filters
それらは最終的に葉フィルターを形成します
The leaf filter is an air pocket inside the plant
葉フィルターは植物の中にある空気のポケットです
Leaf filter eventually it will become
リーフフィルター最終的には
mesophyll cell
葉肉細胞
Post-leaf cells can shape light and function
葉後の細胞は光を形作り機能することができる
finally forming a leaf
ようやく葉が出てきました
This is a construction of a whole plant
プラント全体の工事です
Our genes for the whole inside of the plant
植物の内部全体の遺伝子
mutant strains
変異株
You have a mutation in a single gene
単一遺伝子に突然変異があります
Will affect the plant a lot of changes
植物に多くの変化が影響します
For example, this is inside a tomato
たとえば、これはトマトの中です
a gene that you overexpress
過剰発現する遺伝子
like this gene it controls the leaves
この遺伝子のように葉を制御します
and leaflet development
そしてリーフレットの開発
It turned out to be like this
このようになりました
you can make it like this
このように作ることができます
Therefore, through such a control
したがって、このような制御により、
to express to change a plant's
植物の変化を表現する
The pattern of growth and even its function
成長パターンとその機能
We all know planting
私たちは皆、植栽を知っています
All kinds of planting
あらゆる種類の植栽
In fact, I also caught it from the Internet, and I don't know much about it.
実は私もネットで拾っただけで、あまり詳しくありません。
The only thing I saw was this kind of osmanthus seeds
唯一見たのはこんなキンモクセイの種でした
Other various plantings
その他各種植栽
Planting is an important part of plants
植栽は植物にとって重要な部分です
Why is it other than family reception
なぜ家族接待以外なのか
It is also a food for many animals
多くの動物の食料でもあります
But the whole crop produces
しかし、作物全体が生産するのは、
Must have very successful reproductive growth
生殖成長が非常に成功している必要があります
So our content today
それでは今日の内容は
I will divide it with you and you into these
あなたとあなたでこれに分けます
First, let me tell you about the reproductive system of plants
まず、植物の生殖システムについて説明します。
The second one I will introduce to you
２番目にご紹介するのは
In the past twenty years we have
過去20年間、私たちは
There is something new about the development of a molecular biology cytology tool
分子生物学細胞学ツールの開発には何か新しいことがあります
So how do we use these
では、これらをどのように使用するか
we can explore
私たちは探検することができます
Some questions we may not have been able to explore before
これまで調査できなかったかもしれないいくつかの質問
Finally, I will share with you our research work
最後に私たちの研究成果を紹介します
This is a reproduction of the whole angiosperm
これは被子植物全体の複製です
a life history
一個生活史
Angiosperms differ from other plants in that
被子植物が他の植物と異なる点は、
generations of its counterparts
対応者の世代
Generations of so-called monoquilts
いわゆるモノキルトの世代
very very short
とてもとても短い
For example, this is the male reproductive organs
たとえば、これは男性の生殖器です
female reproductive organ male is anther
女性の生殖器、男性は葯です
Then the female word is
そうすると女性の言葉は、
match it in the fat
脂肪に合わせてください
Then when the anther goes through a split
そして、葯が裂けると、
produce pollen
花粉を生成する
androgenic plant
アンドロゲン植物
So its implant body stage
インプラント本体の段階
just a very short time
ほんの短い時間だけ
Then the embryo sac of the embryo pig
次に、胎芽豚の胎嚢
It is the body of the partner
パートナーの身体です
it has eggs in it
中に卵が入っています
and finally
還有最後
When there is a so-called thin powder effect
いわゆる薄粉効果がある場合
pollen hall
花粉館
From this pollen will be produced the pollen hall
この花粉から花粉ホールが作られます
Finally put it two fine packages
最後に2つの立派なパッケージを入れます
Sent to embryonic pigs to complete double lean muscle
二重引き締まった筋肉を完成させるために胎児期の​​豚に送られる
it's a whole process
それはプロセス全体です
The last skinny egg
最後の痩せた卵
it will continue to develop into a planting
それは植栽へと発展し続けます
This is a life history of the whole plant
これは植物全体の生活史です
so in
それで
let's introduce
紹介しましょう
whole plant reproductive system
植物全体の生殖システム
I will probably split it into two parts
たぶん2回に分けると思います
introduce to you
あなたに紹介します
The first is the sexual reproductive organs of plants
一つ目は植物の生殖器官です。
It is the growth and differentiation of flower teeth
花歯の成長と分化です
For example, flower formation and structure
たとえば、花の形成と構造
Huaya's clones and flower organs
フアヤのクローンと花器官
The second one will introduce to you
２番目にご紹介するのは
The so-called lean powder effect of plants
植物のいわゆるリーンパウダー効果
these partners
これらのパートナー
For example, pollen and the formation of embryonic pigs
たとえば、花粉やブタの胚の形成など
There is also the effect of the whole thin powder
全体の薄いパウダーの効果もあります
So it's a process of selfing
つまり、それは自己化のプロセスです
Wait a minute and you'll know there's something good if you see me
ちょっと待ってください、私に会えば何か良いことがあるでしょう
I want to introduce you to one
一つ紹介したいと思います
This is an experimental material we made
これは私たちが作った実験材料です
called the Arab world
アラブ世界と呼ばれる
Arab world
アラブ世界
It's what we say in terms of our plants
それは私たちが植物に関して言うことです
so-called model plants
いわゆるモデルプラント
like fruit flies or mice
ショウジョウバエやネズミのように
or ant ants
またはアリアリ
These are model plants
これらはモデル植物です
but we plant
しかし私たちは植えます
we are basically arabian
私たちは基本的にアラブ世界です
why it is
なぜそうなるのか
its economy is very small
その経済は非常に小さい
The second its sequencing is done
シーケンスが完了した瞬間
The third
第3
Because all the scientists all over the world
なぜなら世界中の科学者全員が
use this as plant material
これを植物材料として使用します
So there are quite a few resources
かなりのリソースがあるので、
or Internet information
またはインターネット情報
you can find
発見できる
Another one is
もう一つは、
it has many of us now
今では私たちの多くがそれを持っています
so-called insertion with TDNA
いわゆるTDNAによる挿入
mutants
突然変異体
it's okay i'll wait
大丈夫、待ってます
What is TDNA insertion?
TDNA挿入とは何ですか?
There are other mutants
他にも変異体がいる
So when we have a mutant strain of this gene
したがって、この遺伝子の変異株があると、
We know which gene it plugged in
どの遺伝子が組み込まれているかはわかっています
we see what it does
それが何をするか見てみましょう
We can probably infer the function of this gene
おそらくこの遺伝子の機能を推測できるでしょう
So genes get from this information
したがって、遺伝子はこの情報から得られます
So let it be over the past few years
だから、ここ数年はもう終わりにしてください
about ten years
約10年
It makes a very nice plant material
とても素敵な植物素材になります
We can study the genes of plants
植物の遺伝子を研究できる
participate in the development of, for example, pollen
花粉などの開発に関与
Or bear the growth of graft
または移植片の成長に耐える
even pollination and seed growth
受粉と種子の成長が均一になる
For a long time what we called
長い間、私たちが呼んでいたもの
We all know that DNA is our genetic material
DNA が私たちの遺伝物質であることは誰もが知っています
It's a gene it makes a Mason
それはメイソンを作る遺伝子だ
Rapidly follow RNA and finally become protein
RNAを素早くたどり、最終的にタンパク質になる
However, in past research we can find
しかし、過去の研究で分かるのは、
maybe it's not that simple
たぶんそれはそれほど単純ではありません
Possibly RNA could also be a genetic material
おそらくRNAも遺伝物質である可能性があります
For example, our teacher Lin Nazhen
たとえば、私たちの教師である林ナジェン氏は、
The so-called headquarters he discovered
彼が発見したいわゆる本拠地
Bamboo coelovirus
竹コエロウイルス
it is RNA
それはRNAです
but it can be reversed into DNA
しかし、それをDNAに戻すことは可能です
Then turn into RNA and donate into protein
次に RNA になり、タンパク質に寄付されます。
This is a
これは
Another current study found that the so-called
別の最新の研究では、いわゆる
Generics related to production
製造に関連するジェネリック医薬品
none of your genes will change
あなたの遺伝子は何も変わらない
you may see through your
あなたはあなたのことを見透かすかもしれません
change your DNA
DNAを変える
fake plan
偽の計画
or something in your DNA
あるいはあなたのDNAの中にある何か
protein with it
それとプロテイン
False project of binding protein
結合タンパク質の誤ったプロジェクト
Or use sexual expression to control
あるいは性的表現を使ってコントロールする
gene expression
遺伝子発現
So it's not just us anymore
だからもう私たちだけじゃない
It is common to think that such a situation
このような状況だと考えるのが一般的です
This is probably a cartoon
これはおそらく漫画です
The picture can tell you about
写真が伝えることができるのは、
how does the gene go
遺伝子はどうなっているのか
Execute and command
実行とコマンド
Each of these is based on human genes
これらはそれぞれ人間の遺伝子に基づいています
it has a nucleus
核があるんだよ
cell nucleus in plant
植物の細胞核
Another is the plant nucleus
もう一つは植物の核です
Chromosomes inside
内部の染色体
What about each of our chromosomes
私たちのそれぞれの染色体はどうなっているのでしょうか
You see, this is equivalent to
ご覧のとおり、これは次と同等です
the whole gene it winds a
遺伝子全体を巻き上げる
A protein called Histone
ヒストンというタンパク質
This is the DNA
これがDNAです
DNA coils with
DNAコイルと
these inherited messages
受け継がれたこれらのメッセージ
we can call it gene
それを遺伝子と呼ぶことができます
It then acts via detour
その後、迂回して動作します
it seems a little slow
少し遅いようです
that has a protein
タンパク質が入っているもの
It does this thing called DNA RNA polymerase
DNA RNA ポリメラーゼと呼ばれるものを行います
it opens up this genetic structure
それはこの遺伝子構造を開く
Then started doing some messenger RNA
それからメッセンジャー RNA を始めました
Then the messenger RNA of these messages
次に、これらのメッセージのメッセンジャー RNA
then start doing it slowly
それからゆっくりとやり始めます
It is a way to use ATGC to pair with each other
ATGCを利用してペアリングする方法です
to allow it to produce a message RNA like this
このようなメッセージ RNA を生成できるようにする
These last message RNA
最後のメッセージ RNA
and then at the end it goes through some chopping
そして最後にチョッピングが行われます
called messenger RNA
メッセンジャーRNAと呼ばれる
After the final cut
最後切解以後
it will start sending to the cytoplasm
細胞質への送信が始まります
This is what it is in this cell
これがこの細胞の中にあるものです
it cuts some
それはいくらかカットします
put some unwanted things
いらないものを置く
Or we call intron to remove it
または、 intron を呼び出して削除します
Finally turned into a function with
最後に関数になりました
It travels from the nucleus to the cytoplasm
核から細胞質まで移動します
Then in the cytoplasm it will be called by a
その後、細胞質内で、それは
ribexon the concrete
コンクリートのリベキソン
These two electric machines
この２台の電気機械は
Then it's called Rapidzone
それからそれはラピッドゾーンと呼ばれます
This is a ribose base structure
これはリボース塩基構造です
your message it goes along this
あなたのメッセージはこれに沿って進みます
The ribose base is right along the top
リボース塩基は上部に沿ってあります
there are different things
違うことがある
Will put these Transfer RNA above
これらの Transfer RNA を上に置きます
have brought a special IG nucleic acid
特別なIG核酸を持ってきました
It will recognize every Code
あらゆるコードを認識します
In this way, a protein is finally formed
このようにして、最終的にタンパク質が形成されます
it's a whole process
それはプロセス全体です
so i think
だから私は思う
So the growth of the sexual biomass of the whole plant
したがって、植物全体の有性バイオマスの成長
development we want to say
言いたい展開
The first is to introduce
まず紹介するのは、
flowering of plants
植物の開花
its whole bloom
その全開
still formed
まだ形成されていない
whole plant regulator
ホールプラントレギュレーター
probably the flowering of the plant
おそらく植物の開花
by two main factors
2つの主な要因によって
an intrinsic factor
内在的要因
It means that plants must reach a certain stage
植物が一定の段階に到達する必要があることを意味します
like all animals
すべての動物のように
must be mature
成熟していなければなりません
it can bloom
それは咲くことができます
For example, these processes have gene expression for flowering
たとえば、これらのプロセスでは開花のための遺伝子発現が行われます。
or hormonal control
またはホルモン制御
Another external factor
もう一つの外部要因
For example, to have
たとえば、
Length, such as photoperiod
光周期などの長さ
or a low temperature
または低温
The so-called vernalization effect
いわゆる春化効果
The vernalization effect is mainly in the 1st and 2nd year
春化効果は主に1年目と2年目
what about a plant
植物はどうですか
It must undergo a low temperature treatment in seedlings
苗の段階で低温処理が必要です
later its plants will bloom
後にその植物は花を咲かせるでしょう
throughout this process
このプロセス全体を通じて
From this picture you can find
この写真から見つけることができます
Whether it's biological clock, photoperiod, growth and delivery
体内時計、光周期、成長、出産など
Finally, these messages will be
最終的に、これらのメッセージは次のようになります。
are concentrated in a few major ones
いくつかの主要なものに集中している
gene above
上の遺伝子
controlled by these genes
これらの遺伝子によって制御されている
Flower formation throughout the plant
植物全体での花の形成
The development of the whole flower is probably from
花全体の発達はおそらく
the whole top the whole top of the branch
枝の上部全体 枝の上部全体
All top inflorescence clones
すべての上位花序クローン
it will form this flower tooth clone
それはこの花の歯のクローンを形成します
That is Flameris etc.
それがフラメリスなどです。
this is the inflorescence
これが花序です
Then this is the clone with flower teeth
それからこれは花の歯を持ったクローンです
Then grow with infinity
そして無限に成長します
For the branches of that plant
その植物の枝に
Its flower teeth are basically limited growth
花歯は基本的に成長が限られています
when this place forms a flower
この場所に花が咲くとき
it stops growing
成長が止まる
So in the end, different flower vessels will be formed
最終的には、さまざまな花器が形成されるでしょう
like, say, primitive cells
たとえば原始細胞のような
Finally there are the primitive cells of this flower organ
最後に、この花器官の原始細胞があります。
finally form the whole flower
最後に花全体を形成します
The structure of this flower is probably like this
この花の構造はおそらくこんな感じ
Let's talk about the model plant in the Arabian world
アラビア世界のモデルプラントについて話しましょう
It has about four from the outside to the inside
外側から内側まで4つくらいあります
There are four flowers
花が４つあります
then there are four petals
それから花びらは4枚です
But there are six stamens in the middle
でも真ん中におしべが6本ある
Finally in the middle are two fused cores
最後に中央に 2 つの融合コアがあります
it's a typical
それは典型的なものです
everyone remember
誰もが覚えています
wait a minute it will have a little quiz
ちょっと待ってください、ちょっとしたクイズがあります
little quiz
ちょっとしたクイズ
tell everyone
みんなに言ってください
Genes involved in flowering flower buds
花芽の開花に関与する遺伝子
For example, this gene that controls flower bud formation
たとえば、花芽の形成を制御するこの遺伝子は、
There are two clones and flowers
2 つのアバターと花があります
then or bowl
それからまたはボウル
Bowl control over fat development
脂肪の発達を制御するボウル
And how do we know which genes
そしてどの遺伝子をどのようにして知ることができるのでしょうか
control the whole process
プロセス全体を制御する
The most important thing is the mutant strain we just talked about
最も重要なことは、先ほど話した変異株です。
When you have a mutation in one of your genes
遺伝子のいずれかに突然変異があると、
You can find that the shape of the flower has changed
花の形が変わっているのがわかります
For example, it has more stamens
たとえば、雄しべが多い
or more petals
またはそれ以上の花びら
you know the gene
あなたは遺伝子を知っていますか
presumably involved in the process
おそらくプロセスに関与している
So many scientists
とてもたくさんの科学者が
After slowly accumulating
ゆっくり積み上げてから
By now we probably know that there are
今ではおそらく、
This is the whole Arab world
これがアラブ世界全体だ
From planting all the way to the whole flower
植え付けから花全体まで
this way of planting
この植え方
such as controlling flower buds
花芽の制御など
you don't want to go
行きたくないですか
you just go to the Internet to check
インターネットにアクセスして確認するだけです
probably many
おそらく多くの
Basically two types
おそらく大きく分けて2種類
The first is to promote the formation of flower bud differentiation tissue
1つ目は、花芽分化組織の形成を促進することです。
For example like LIFI
たとえばLIFIのような
or AP2
またはAP2
these things
これらの事
these genes
これらの遺伝子
Another one that maintains the flower buds into tissue
花芽を組織内に維持するもう 1 つの方法
Let's say this is the Arab world
ここがアラブ世界だとしましょう
traditional one normal phenotype
伝統的な 1 つの正常な表現型
But you help you with a gene called LIFI
でもあなたはLIFIという遺伝子であなたを助けます
when like a leaf
葉っぱのようなとき
it was originally supposed to be where the flower was
本来はそこに花があるはずだった
it becomes like a leaf
葉っぱのようになる
So you know why it's called LIFI
LIFI と呼ばれる理由がわかります
LIFI is like a leaf
LIFIは葉っぱのようなもの
flower tooth formation
花歯の形成
Also, for example, this
また、例えばこれ
When you find out with another
他の人にわかったら
it should stop flowering in this place
この場所では花が咲かなくなるはずです
But with Dang LIFI and another
でも、Dang LIFIと別の人とは
they keep growing
彼らは成長し続けます
So you say that when these two genes can
つまり、これら 2 つの遺伝子ができるようになると、
just under control
ちょうどコントロール下にある
This place should form a flower later
この場所は後で花を咲かせるはずです
should stop
やめるべきだ
But when these two genes are mutated
しかし、これら 2 つの遺伝子が突然変異すると、
it can keep growing
成長し続けることができる
Another one like Terminal Flower
もう一つはターミナルフラワーのようなもの
That is to say, the gene
つまり遺伝子は
It just mutates there
ただそこで変異するだけだ
there will be no such flowers
そんな花はないだろう
so this is a whole you can go and see
これはあなたが行って見ることができる全体です
the first one so this is the control flower tooth
最初のものなので、これがコントロールの花の歯です
But what about after the flower teeth are born?
では、花歯が生えた後はどうでしょうか？
there will be flowers
花があるでしょう
flower organ
花器官
have a model
モデルがいる
Called ABC model
ABCモデルと呼ばれる
is very famous
とても有名です
look at
見る
A gene controls the second round
遺伝子が第2ラウンドを制御する
flower vessel formation
花器形成
A gene alone controls the first round
遺伝子だけが最初のラウンドを制御する
The B gene controls the formation of the second and third rounds
B 遺伝子は第 2 ラウンドと第 3 ラウンドの形成を制御します。
flower vessel formation
花器形成
C gene controls third and fourth rounds
C遺伝子は第3ラウンドと第4ラウンドを制御する
A gene alone controls the fourth round
遺伝子だけが第4ラウンドを制御する
Resist each other
お互いに抵抗し合う
who can understand
誰が理解できますか
probably many do not understand
おそらく多くの人は理解していません
But people use scientists to use this way
しかし人々は科学者をこのように利用する
oh
おお
A gene alone controls the first round
遺伝子だけが最初のラウンドを制御する
then B gene
次にB遺伝子
B gene controls the first and second rounds
B遺伝子は第1ラウンドと第2ラウンドを制御する
second round
第二輪
So use something like this
したがって、このようなものを使用してください
a mechanism for this
このためのメカニズム
Then the C gene alone
そうするとC遺伝子だけが
Control is the fourth round
コントロールは4ラウンド目
Xiong Rui
シオン・ルイ
But the A genes neutralize each other
しかし、A遺伝子は互いに中和し合う
That is, when the C gene is broken
つまり、C遺伝子が壊れると、
it occupies
それは占有します
Gene A came running
ジーンAが走って来た
Occupies the position of the A gene
A遺伝子の位置を占めます
remember
覚えて
ok let's take the test now
よし、今からテストを受けよう
There will be prizes in the exam
試験では賞品が出ます
This is what I was looking for today
今日探していたものはこれです
please us yesterday
昨日私たちにお願いします
An administrator, Tingyu, he did it
管理者のティンギュ、彼はやった
This is when our campus is open
キャンパスがオープンするのはこの時期です
Shi Hulan's organization seconds
シー・フーランの組織秒数
guessed right
推測が正しかった
Answer the question correctly
質問に正しく答えてください
Okay, let's see when the A gene is mutated
さて、A 遺伝子がいつ突然変異するかを見てみましょう
what will happen to it
それはどうなりますか
so tell who can raise their hand
だから誰が手を挙げられるか教えてください
tell me what the first round turns out to be
最初のラウンドがどうなるか教えてください
what happens in the first round
最初のラウンドで何が起こるか
good
良い
ok so what will it be
さて、それではどうなるでしょうか
Xiong Rui, Ci Rui, right?
シオン・ルイ、シー・ルイですよね？
Okay, the second one, you raised your hand, you have to finish it
わかりました、2 つ目、あなたは手を挙げました、あなたはそれを終わらせなければなりません
What about the second round?
2回戦はどうなるの？
What is BC gold, what will mutual pursuit be
BCゴールドとは何か、相互追求とは何か
BC Jin Xiongrui at any time, right?
いつでもBC金雄瑞ですよね？
You have to tell me Xiongrui, Cirui, flower petals
教えてよ シオンルイ、シルイ、花びら
What about the third one?
3番目はどうでしょうか？
good great fourth
良い、素晴らしい 4 番目
Okay, so if you don't know what it grows like
さて、それがどのように成長するかわからない場合は、
So this is such a plant
これはそういう植物なんですね
Come on, Mr. Zhou, please help me to give it to him
さあ、周さん、彼に渡すのを手伝ってください。
Okay, so you can find the words where the petals should be
よし、花びらがあるべき場所に単語が見つかるよ
it is now xiong rui
今はション・ルイです
So you can't tell it's not quite a flower at all
だから、それがまったく花ではないということはわかりません
We have A B C three golds and two chances
A B C 3 つの金メダルと 2 つのチャンスがあります
The second one, does anyone know when B gold has a mutation?
2つ目は、Bゴールドがいつ突然変異を起こすか知っている人はいますか？
what happens in the first round
最初のラウンドで何が起こるか
Hurry up, it's beautiful
急いでください、それは美しいです
It's been a long time today and it's blooming
今日は久しぶりに開花しました
Hands up, what's the first round?
挙手、最初のラウンドは何ですか?
good second round
良い第二ラウンド
third
三番目
Xiong Rui
シオン・ルイ
Fourth, well, I'll give you another chance
4番目、まあ、もう一度チャンスを与えるよ
Cirui good
シルイ良い
OK this is the flower you think it looks like a flower
OK、これがあなたが花のように見えると思う花です
come to you
あなたのところに来てください
good third
良い3番目
last chance sorry
最後のチャンスごめんなさい
only one left
1つだけ残っている
Advertise our position willing to open
喜んでオープンする当社のポジションを宣伝します
every year there will be this
毎年これがあるでしょう
Welcome to our office next year
来年も私たちのオフィスへようこそ
you can get it, you can get it
あなたはそれを得ることができます、あなたはそれを得ることができます
Not getting it, it may take a little EVER to change it
理解できません。変更するには少し時間がかかるかもしれません
good third suck
3回目はいいですね
When Sucking Mutations
突然変異を吸うとき
What would be the mutation A
突然変異Aは何になるでしょうか
what's the first one at least raise your hand
最初のものは何ですか、少なくとも手を挙げてください
good
良い
flower two are you sure
花 2 本当ですか
What about the second one?
2番目のものはどうですか？
Let's see what it looks like
どのようなものかを見てみましょう
it's cool there are flowers in flowers
涼しいですね、花の中に花があります
If you are running the original hydraulic power at home today
現在、自宅で元の水力発電を実行している場合
Then you want to pre-summary
次に、事前に概要を説明します。
This would be a great plant material
これは素晴らしい植物素材になるでしょう
Why
なぜ
it can only be bought like you
それはあなたのようにしか買えません
you don't produce seeds
あなたは種を生産しません
but there are flowers in your flowers
でもあなたの花には花がある
isn't it beautiful
綺麗じゃないですか
it's a pretty good one
それはかなり良いものです
So this is the ABC gene
これがABC遺伝子です
But scientists never give up
しかし科学者たちは決して諦めない
never satisfied
決して満足しない
they think so
彼らはそう思う
Because after you mutate all the ABC genes
なぜなら、ABC遺伝子をすべて変異させた後だからです。
but put it all in the plant
でもそれをすべて工場に入れてください
everyone has performance
誰もがパフォーマンスを持っています
you didn't turn it into a flower
あなたはそれを花に変えなかった
later they found out
後で彼らは知った
BC gene
BC遺伝子
when it's going to work
それがうまくいくとき
they will find
彼らは見つけます
There is another group of genes
別の遺伝子グループがあります
called SEP-123
SEP-123と呼ばれる
These three genes are very similar
これら 3 つの遺伝子は非常に似ています
they are going to work together
彼らは一緒に働くつもりです
When your three genes
あなたの 3 つの遺伝子が
After SEP-123 is mutated
SEP-123が変異した後
The whole plant will turn into a flower evil
植物全体が花の悪に変わります
so they finally know
それで彼らはついに知った
at this place
この場所で
In fact, the role of the BC gene
実際、BC遺伝子の役割は、
need to use
使用する必要があります
Involvement of the E gene
E遺伝子の関与
So they thought it was a very important
それで彼らはそれが非常に重要だと考えました
For example, this is a normal flower in the Arab world
たとえば、これはアラブ世界では普通の花です
This is a mutation in the E gene
これはE遺伝子の突然変異です
you take it apart we say outside in
あなたはそれを分解します、私たちはアウトサイドインと言います
four flowers two
四つの花 二つ
four petals
4枚の花びら
six stamens
雄しべが6本
The ratio of two fused hearts
融合する2つの心の割合
But you can find that it looks exactly like Hua Er
しかし、それはHua Erにそっくりであることがわかります
This looks a lot like a mutation in the BC gene
これはBC遺伝子の突然変異によく似ています
so they know
だから彼らは知っている
The BC gene must be together with the E gene in the future
BC遺伝子は将来E遺伝子と一緒になるはずです
they only use
彼らはただ使用します
so you can see that it's not just a morphological change
単なる形態変化ではないことがわかります
When your gene is mutated
遺伝子が突然変異すると
on our exterior
弊社の外装に
You see we're using an electron microscope
電子顕微鏡を使っているのがわかりますね
Look at the electron microscope
電子顕微鏡を見てください
In normal Wildtide
通常のワイルドタイドでは
normal bead words
通常のビーズの言葉
Its flowers look like they have blowholes on them
その花は吹き穴があるように見えます
it's green
これは緑です
You can find that it has pores for photosynthesis
光合成のための穴があることがわかります。
Its petal shape is like this
花びらの形はこんな感じです
but when you
しかし、あなたが
When a gene is mutated
遺伝子が突然変異すると
you look like flower even in the petals
あなたは花びらまで花のように見えます
So you're not only a waigan change
だからあなたは単なる変化者ではないのです
You change even its very nature
あなたはその本質さえも変えてしまう
So in the end people are now
結局のところ、人々は今、
There is a called ABCE Model
ABCEモデルと呼ばれるものがあります
For example, for the first one this time, you want to control the second petal of the flower
たとえば、今回の 1 つ目では、花の 2 番目の花びらを制御したいとします。
You need the ABCE gene to make different combinations
さまざまな組み合わせを行うには ABCE 遺伝子が必要です
I don't think there is any need to remember this.
これは覚える必要はないと思います。
But that is to say it has a
しかし、それは、
So is there something else involved?
では、他に何か関係があるのでしょうか？
Yes
はい
Because there are still people in the land and land area who have discovered
陸地にはまだ発見した人がいるから
Others may have other proteins involved
他のものには他のタンパク質が関与している可能性があります
for example
例えば
When your other gene is mutated
他の遺伝子が変異すると
You know why it's called Superman
なぜスーパーマンと呼ばれるか知っていますか
Because it has a lot of stamens
雄しべがたくさんあるので
When your Superman gene mutates
スーパーマンの遺伝子が変異すると
Its stamens will increase
雄しべが増えます
Or if you look at this, it has
あるいは、これを見てみると、
it will have excessive flowering
過剰な開花が起こるでしょう
Like this one we just should have a normal flower with
この花のように、普通の花を使えばいいのです。
four petals
4枚の花びら
You can find it this florescence this
あなたはそれを見つけることができます、この蛍光
have changed
変更されました
even this doesn't look like a flower at all
これでも全然花に見えない
So this is all made of these mutant beads
つまり、これはすべてこれらの突然変異ビーズで作られています
research we can
私たちにできる研究
we accumulate
私たちは蓄積します
we can slowly know
私たちはゆっくりと知ることができます
How do these genes get involved
これらの遺伝子はどのように関与するのか
the whole flower
花全体
Differentiation and development of flower buds
花芽の分化と発達
Even the formation of flower organs
花器官の形成も
the role they play
彼らが果たす役割
In fact, there is quite a lot of space
実際はかなり広いスペースがあります
For young students who are interested
興味のある若い学生さんへ
or other interested
またはその他の興味のあるもの
and a big one
そして大きなもの
A space for research and development
研究開発のためのスペース
The second one I will introduce to you
２番目にご紹介するのは
the so-called pollination of plants
いわゆる植物の受粉
What we can talk about first is the so-called configuration body
まず最初に説明できるのは、いわゆる構成本体についてです。
Formation of pollen exudation
花粉滲出液の形成
pollination
受粉
and the mechanism of pollen tube growth
花粉管の成長メカニズムと
this is a whole plant
これは植物全体です
You can find from here to here
ここからここまで見つかります
the most important is
最も重要なことは
diploid on this side
こちら側の二倍体
when you go through a deceleration split
減速スプリットを通過するとき
your so-called
あなたのいわゆる
this is pollen
これは花粉です
will form pollen
会形成花粉
Pollen mother cells make pollen
花粉母細胞が花粉を作る
pollen tube
花粉管
This is the last and this is the embryo
これが最後で、これが胚です
The central cell will form a
中央細胞は、
so-called embryo sac
いわゆる胎嚢
There are three anti-bamboo cells inside
内部には3つの抗竹セルがあります
a central cell
中央細胞
an egg
卵
Next to it are two saprophytic cells
その隣には2つの腐生細胞があります
this is the last
これが最後です
it's a whole
それは全体です
throughout the developmental process
発達過程全体を通して
how do you know this situation
この状況をどうやって知っていますか
because it's still the same
それは今も同じだから
Tubian Bamboo
管状竹
so far
ここのところ
this is what we are talking about
これが私たちが話していることです
In fact, you can see this in 2008
実際、これは 2008 年にも見られます
But over the past 10 years
しかし、ここ10年ほどで
more genes found
さらに多くの遺伝子が見つかった
But first with this
でもまずはこれで
in the thoracic stamen
胸部雄しべにある
You can find that the most important thing is
最も重要なことは次のとおりであることがわかります。
pollen mother cell
花粉母細胞
And this big embryo
そしてこの大きな胎芽は
Mother cells they go through like this
彼らはこのようにして母細胞を通過します
you can find
発見できる
every gene
あらゆる遺伝子
every process
あらゆるプロセス
Here is a genetic mutation
ここに遺伝子変異があります
will affect this
これに影響します
so we accumulate
だから私たちは蓄積します
We can know that
私たちはそれを知ることができます
all these genes
これらすべての遺伝子
in the middle of this whole process
このプロセス全体の途中で
role involved
関与する役割
you don't have to remember
覚えておく必要はありません
because i can't remember
思い出せないから
But on these files
しかし、これらの書類に関しては、
can be found
見つけることができます
but so later
でもそれはまた後で
let's do some more research
もっと研究してみましょう
because we see what happens to this pollen at some stage
なぜなら、ある段階でこの花粉に何が起こるのかが分かるからです。
We can go back to the literature and think
文献に戻って考えることができます
It turned out that the gene was mutated
遺伝子が変異していることが判明
Is our gene a protein? Does it have any interaction with it?
私たちの遺伝子はタンパク質ですか?相互作用はありますか?
we can make progress
私たちは進歩することができます
So this is some of our information in that place
これはその場所での情報の一部です
whole pollination
整個受粉作用
The whole pollination basically the pollination of plants is
受粉全体とは基本的に植物の受粉は次のとおりです。
Pollen is an extremely dry condition
花粉は極度の乾燥状態です
When the pollen is ripening it dehydrates
花粉が成熟すると脱水状態になる
it will have a dehydration
脱水症状になります
so the pollen falls on the stigma
それで花粉が柱頭に落ちます
The pollen then absorbs water on the stigma
花粉は柱頭の水分を吸収します。
But this process has to go through a lot of so-called cell-to-cell interactions
しかし、このプロセスでは、いわゆる細胞間の相互作用を数多く通過する必要があります。
For example, in the plant kingdom, there is a thing called self-inferiority and credible
たとえば、植物界には自己劣位と信頼性というものがあります。
That is to say, your own pool core will repel
つまり、自分のプールコアが反発してしまいます。
or keep yourself from pollen with the same genotype
または同じ遺伝子型の花粉から身を守る
One may be absorbing water on the stigma
柱頭で水を吸収している可能性があります
self-ambiguity
自己曖昧さ
But if it's inside the style
でもそれがスタイルの中にあるなら
Let it grow to a certain stage
一定の段階まで成長させましょう
Don't let it be long is ligand body
長くしないでください、それはリガンド本体です
self ambiguous
自交不清核性
I won't be there today
今日はそこにいません
Because the mechanism is very, very complicated
仕組みがとても複雑なので、
Finally the pollen hall will enter the style after the growth
成長を経ていよいよ花粉殿がスタイルに入ります
Finally two packets of information will be
最後に、2 つの情報パケットが次のようになります。
Send to distribution to complete double collection
配布に送信して二重回収を完了する
Throughout this process you may have
このプロセス全体を通じて、次のようなことが起こる可能性があります
There are bee plum blossoms or insect plum blossoms
蜂梅や虫梅もあります
You can take the pollen with you
花粉も持ち運べる
When the last pollen is on the stigma
最後の花粉が柱頭についたとき
it will generate a
それは生成します
This is the epidermis of the stigma
これが柱頭の表皮です
That epidermal cell that produces pollen tubes
花粉管を作る表皮細胞
Eventually the pollen hall will grow inside the style
やがて花柱の中に花粉ホールが成長していきます
This is the practice style
これが練習スタイルです
you can look under a microscope
顕微鏡で見ることができます
You go dye a special thing called
あなたは特別なものを染めに行きます。
dye
染料
you can see
見ることができます
Every growth is a pollen hall
すべての成長は花粉ホールです
These little bits are called Kalus Pluck
この小さな子たちはカルス・プラックと呼ばれています
It's the pollen hall that keeps growing
増殖し続ける花粉殿です
in the middle
途中で
It keeps forming structures like this
このような構造を形成し続けます
only let
だけさせてください
The tip of the pollen is alive
花粉の先端は生きている
That place brings two exquisite
あの場所は二つの素晴らしいものをもたらします
I once did an experiment
かつて実験をしたことがある
After losing weight
体重を減らした後
you put that stigma
あなたはその汚名を着せた
And part of the pollen style is removed
花粉風の一部を除去
as long as you keep the topmost pollen structure intact
最上部の花粉構造を無傷に保つ限り
it last it doesn't need
それは最後です、それは必要ありません
have used those pollen tubes or
それらの花粉管を使用したことがある、または
Thin Gold
薄いゴールド
you turn it upside down
あなたはそれを逆さまにします
It can still grow slower
まだ成長が遅くなる可能性があります
because of this kind of place
こういう場所だから
But you can still lose gold
しかし、それでもゴールドを失う可能性はあります
so you know it's a very
それはとても素晴らしいことです
Active means magnetic sharp
アクティブとは磁気鋭利を意味します
will send a message
メッセージを送信します
Attracts pollen tubes to my kind
私の種類に花粉管を引き寄せる
This is a hollow style
これは中空スタイルです
For example like we have
たとえば、私たちが持っているように
One of our experimental materials
実験材料の一つ
Iron Cannon Lily
アイアンキャノンリリー
You can spot these pollen tubes
これらの花粉管を見つけることができます
grows along the inner epidermal cells
内側の表皮細胞に沿って成長します
Pollen tubes are what we just talked about
花粉管は先ほど話したものです
this tip
このヒント
what you see under the tip microscope
先端顕微鏡の下で何が見えるか
The previous one is a
前のものは、
just very very
ただとてもとても
seems to be a clean place
きれいな場所のようです
seen under a microscope
顕微鏡で見た
It is a lot of different packages
色々なパッケージがありますが、
in this whole structure
この構造全体の中で
last this
最後にこれ
This pollen hall is constantly being formed
この花粉ホールは常に形成され続けています
The so-called Kelas Park
いわゆるケラスパーク
take this pollen house
この花粉ハウスを持って行ってください
So in the end you just need this place to finish
だから最終的にはこの場所だけで終わる必要があるんだ
Take it today to put the last two gold cells
今すぐ最後の 2 つのゴールド セルを配置してください
to that pool
あのプールへ
Match pigs to complete double insemination
豚をマッチングして二重授精を完了する
So the last two gold cells
つまり、最後の 2 つの金のセルは
This pollen shop will deliver
この花粉屋がお届けします
This place is called the pig hole
ここは豚穴と呼ばれる場所です
complete fertilization
完全な受精
For example, this is one percent of our iron pack
たとえば、これは鉄パックの 1 パーセントです。
You can find out if you look hard enough
よく探せばわかるよ
This is a pig hole, this is an embryonic pig
これは豚の穴、これは胎児の豚です
this is fat
これは太っています
you can discover a pollen house
花粉の家を発見できます
just go in from here
ここから入ってください
So throughout the
だから全体を通して、
Speaking of the double fertilization of plants as a whole
植物全体の重複受精について言えば、
probably
おそらく
so a pollen house
それで花粉の家
last middle gold
最後中間一個金子
Pollen hall is the bear plastosome
花粉ホールはクマの色素体です
Its purpose is to combine two gold cells
その目的は、2 つのゴールドセルを結合することです。
sent to this embryo sac
この胎嚢に送られます
Embryo sac should be double fertilized
胚嚢は重複受精する必要があります
one of them will follow
彼らのうちの一人が従うでしょう
egg is soft fertilization
卵子は軟体受精です
double fertilization
重複受精
a sperm will follow it
精子はそれに従うだろう
In addition, it will follow this polar cell
さらに、この極セルに続きます
cell center
細胞中心
The two poles in the central cell
中央セルの 2 つの極
complete fertilization
完成受精
So how much is 1 plus 1 equal to an egg?
では、1プラス1に等しい卵は何ですか?
2 is 2n
2は2nです
But in the end this central cell
でも結局この中央細胞は
What will this fertilized central cell form
この受精した中央細胞は何を形成するのでしょうか
breastfeeding
母乳育児
So the seed of the plant is very special
つまり、植物の種子は非常に特別です
it belongs to 3n
それは3nに属します
so it is triploid
だから三倍体だよ
So this is a very special construct
これは非常に特殊な構造です
And finally after this fertilized egg
そして最後にこの受精卵の後に
It will eventually go through a series of fetal development
最終的には一連の胎児発育を経る
will generate interval
間隔が生成されます
the last seed formed
最後に形成された種
The following is probably
おそらく以下は、
How to grow the high efficiency of this cartoon
この漫画の高効率の成長方法
a pollen tube
花粉管
Inside the pollen tube are two sperm cells
花粉管の中には2つの精細胞があります
will go in along the bead hole
ビーズの穴に沿って入っていきます
There should be a bead hole in it
ビーズの穴があるはずです
from one of the two so-called saprophytic cells
いわゆる2つの腐生細胞のうちの1つから
destroyed
破壊されました
So in the end one of the sperm cells
それで最終的には精子細胞の1つが
will follow this soft cell
このソフトセルに従います
complete fertilization
完成受精
form what is called a Zygote
形成所謂的一個Zygote
is to receive nuclei
核を受け取ることです
This is rotten cell
これは腐った細胞です
Rot cells, this is pink cells
腐った細胞、これはピンクの細胞です
So one of them will follow it
それで彼らのうちの一人がそれに従うでしょう
Also this is a central cell that has a collection
また、これはコレクションを持つ中央セルです
The central cell communicates with it
中央セルはそれと通信します
So far, probably the above three are called antipodal cells
今のところ、おそらく上記の 3 つが対蹠細胞と呼ばれています
as far as I know
私の知る限りでは
now it must be working
今は動いているはずです
Just like everyone has a length
誰にでも長さがあるように
People think that Mangchang is nothing
人々は望昌を何もないと思っている
but found
でも見つかった
May now find out that Mang Chang actually
今ならマン・チャンが実際にいることを知るかもしれない
In fact, it has some functions
実はこれにはいくつかの機能があり、
I don't know what it does
何をするのか分かりません
It's just that people say it's useful
便利だと言っているだけです
So I guess the three antipodal cells
つまり、3つの対蹠細胞だと思います
It's not clear what effect
どのような効果があるのか​​は不明
So it's probably over
だから多分終わったんだろうね
Finally this will form the so-called Peyru
最終的にこれはいわゆるペイルを形成します
This will form the so-called Pey
これはいわゆるペイを形成します
This is a photo of the whole
こちらは全体の写真です
Gum plant
ガムの植物
plant glue
植物接着剤
We just talked about the ones with stone cores
石の芯を持つものについて話しました
For example, like our so-called Arab world
たとえば、いわゆるアラブ世界のように
or hollow
または中空
This is Iron Cannon Baihe
アイアンキャノンバイヘです
You can find this is them these pollen houses will go along this
これが花粉ハウスがこれに沿って進むことを見つけることができます
So in the middle of the pollination process?
ということは、受粉プロセスの途中でしょうか？
From the whole stigma pollen falling on the stigma to being completely fat
柱頭全体の花粉が柱頭に落ちて完全に太るまで
Embryo pigs look throughout and find that there are two pollen halls in the middle of the process
胚の豚は全体を観察し、プロセスの途中に 2 つの花粉ホールがあることを発見します。
Two shop terms means one
2 つのショップ用語は 1 つを意味します
it's like we're going home today
今日は家に帰るみたいだ
you are now on freeway
あなたは今高速道路にいます
When you get to the freeway, you see
高速道路に出ると見えます
i live in taoyuan
私は桃園に住んでいます
I saw Taoyuan
桃園が見えてきました
I'm leaving home
家を出ます
right
右
out of the house
家の外で
you want to go back to your car park
自宅に戻って駐車場の準備をしたい
do you still have a term
まだ任期はありますか
so it's like finally he's going home
それで、ついに彼は家に帰るみたいです
So he has two shop terms
つまり、彼には 2 つのショップタームがある
These two are very, very important
この2つはとてもとても重要です
And now scientists are researching that
そして今、科学者たちはそれを研究しています
in the middle of this whole process
このプロセス全体の途中で
A shop term is called funical
店用語では「ファニカル」といいます。
It's a guiding for pig pie
ピッグパイのご案内です
pollen hall
花粉館
it has to sense
それは感知しなければならない
message from the gametophyte
配偶体からのメッセージ
Told you that you were coming out of here
ここから出てくるって言ったね
i'm here he's going in
私はここにいます、彼は入っていきます
The other one is from Zhukou
もう一人は周口出身です
he will
彼は
So only two attract
だから二人だけが惹かれる
for example
例えば
when you plant
植えるとき
Under normal conditions of this pollen
この花粉の通常の条件下では
Every
毎日
AmbroSecPanel
アンブロセックパネル
Will only accept one pollen tube
花粉管は1本しか受け付けない
so there will only be one pollen tube
したがって花粉管は1本だけになります
along the bead handle
ビードハンドルに沿って
will enter the micropyle to complete the double release
微小門に入り、二重放出を完了します
When you plant this it doesn't matter
これを植えたら問題ない
when holding the gametophyte
配偶体を持つとき
it's basically
それは基本的にです
Pollen will not recognize Signal
花粉は信号を認識しない
But other times when some plants mutate
しかし、一部の植物が突然変異する場合もあります
For example called Marmut
たとえばマルムットと呼ばれる
when you do this it can
これを行うと、それができます
along the micropyle
微丘に沿って
To go along this Funicle is the bead handle
このフニクルに沿って進むにはビードハンドルが必要です
it can pollen tubes know where to come out
花粉管はどこから出てくるかを知ることができるのか
but it can't find a home
しかし家が見つからない
When this gene is mutated
この遺伝子が変異すると
You can find all the pollen tubes
すべての花粉管を見つけることができます
can only go around outside
外を回ることしかできない
It can't find the micropyle of McPad
McPad の小パイルが見つかりません
so you know the gene
それで遺伝子を知っていますか
When a mutation occurs, there are two
突然変異が起こると、次の 2 つが起こります。
First
初め
when your gene is mutated
遺伝子が突然変異すると
Your pollen tube can't help
花粉管は役に立たない
sense to this from Chirui
チルイからこれを感じる
Embryo sac kidney out information
胚嚢腎アウト情報
the second
二番目
Each of our original bead handles
それぞれのオリジナルビーズハンドル
only one pollen tube
花粉管は1本だけ
You can find quite a few pollen tubes
かなりの数の花粉管が見つかります
so you know the role it's involved in
それで、それがどのような役割を果たしているかがわかります
The messaging is in this section
メッセージはこのセクションにあります
In addition there is this mute
さらにこんなミュートもあります
you can spot pollen tubes
花粉管を見つけることができます
Yes, the normal pollen tubes I just talked about
はい、先ほどお話しした正常な花粉管です。
Go in from McPa
マクパから入る
After this beadhole goes in
このビーズホールが入った後
pollen tubes will burst
花粉管が破裂してしまう
Exploding will release two gold pieces
爆発すると金貨が2つ放出される
but this you can find
しかし、これは見つかります
When your gene mutates
遺伝子が変異すると
Pollen tubes can go in along the stalk
花粉管は茎に沿って進入することができます
Micropyretes can also be found
マイクロパイレットも見つかります
But it won't explode after it goes in
でも入った後は爆発しない
so you can know
それであなたは知ることができます
The role of this gene
この遺伝子の役割
Eventually the pollen tube will burst
やがて花粉管が破裂してしまう
Release the two economic packages
二つの経済対策の発表
So in this process there is quite a lot of
このプロセスでは、非常に多くの作業が行われます。
a study of
の研究
Only then can we know how the entire pollen tube is frightened
そうして初めて、花粉管全体がどのように怯えているかを知ることができるのです。
So now we're going to just ask
それでは、次に質問してみましょう
scientists are never satisfied
科学者は決して満足しない
these molecules
これらの分子
pool core
プールコア
Or these pool configuration bodies sent out by it
または、それによって送信されるこれらのプール構成本体
how did it come out
どうやって出てきたのですか
where did it come from
それはどこから来たの
So there is a scientist who just use the tight
科学者がいて、彼らはただタイトなものを使っているだけです
material of this plant
この植物の材料
What's so special about this plant material?
この植物素材の何がそんなに特別なのでしょうか?
it has a bare
それは裸を持っています
embrane
膜
the scientist
科学者
He's a pretty good guy
彼はかなりいい奴だよ
Their article was published in Science
彼らの論文は Science 誌に掲載されました
what's so special about this plant
この植物の何が特別なのか
That is to say, it matches
つまり合ってる
We used to pack this bag in it.
私たちはこのバッグに詰めていました。
but this one it's all exposed
でもこれは全部暴露されてる
After you separate the accessory sac
付属袋を切り離したら
put it on your garnish
飾りに付けてください
You put it in the pollen hall
花粉ホールに置いたのね
you can find
発見できる
This is the so-called Mike Pie
これがいわゆるマイク・パイです
It's pig's mouth
豚の口だよ
you can find
発見できる
This is the pollen hall that grows outside the body
これは体の外に成長する花粉ホールです
will naturally run in
自然と流れ込んでくる
complete fertilization
完成受精
you can find
発見できる
Enter through the middle of the two rotting spiders
腐った二匹の蜘蛛の真ん中を通って入る
it completes fertilization
それは受精を完了します
They found a system like this
彼らはこのようなシステムを見つけました
so he wants
だから彼は望んでいる
This is a very good system
これはとても良いシステムです
at least we know
少なくとも私たちは知っています
embryo sac
胎嚢
There are two rot lizards inside
中には腐ったトカゲが2匹います
a central cell
一個中央細胞
one more egg
もう一つの卵
And the above three anti-bamboo cells
そして上記の3つの抗竹細胞
three anti-bamboo cells
三個反竹細胞
maybe too far
遠すぎるかもしれない
they got here
彼らはここに着きました
At least we just look at the following
少なくとも次のことを確認するだけです
I went in with the pollen house
花粉ハウスと一緒に行ってきました
The carrion is more important
腐ったトカゲのほうが重要だ
eggs are more important
卵比較重要
or the central cell is more important
あるいは中央細胞の方が重要です
So they made a
そこで彼らは、
very interesting experiment
とても興味深い実験
controlled by laser
レーザーで制御される
look
見て
They can use a combination of laser and microscope
レーザーと顕微鏡を組み合わせて使用​​できます
It can be destroyed with great precision
かなりの精度で破壊できる
One of the
一つ
i can destroy
私は破壊することができます
Between the two rot packs
2 つの腐敗パックの間
Destroy this Centro cell
このセントロセルを破壊する
or two rotten cells
または腐った細胞が2つ
You destroy it with one hit of the laser
レーザーの一撃で破壊できる
So you use various permutations
したがって、さまざまな順列を使用します
Destroys the morphology of various cells
さまざまな細胞の形態を破壊する
You can make a result like this
このような結果を作ることができます
i can destroy a cell
細胞を破壊できる
destroy two cells
2つの細胞を破壊する
destroy three cells
3つの細胞を破壊する
various combinations
さまざまな組み合わせ
We look at it for the whole ability to attract pollen tubes
花粉管を誘引する能力全体を調べる
Will it be affected
影響はありますか
So in the end they found
それで最終的に彼らは見つけたのです
a fun one is
楽しいことは
when you find out
わかったとき
You just need a rotten cell
必要なのは腐った細胞だけだ
Next to it are the two cells next to the soft
その隣にはソフトの隣の 2 つのセルがあります。
As long as one rotten cell is broken
腐った細胞がひとつ壊れるかぎり
It's basically the ability to attract pollen tubes in
基本的には花粉管を引き寄せる能力です。
just lower
ただ下に
Once you help put these two rotten cells
この 2 つの腐った細胞を配置するのを手伝ってくれたら
when completely destroyed
完全に破壊されたとき
Pollen tubes do not enter
花粉管が入らない
so what do they know
それで彼らは何を知っているのですか
This signal is sent from two rotting cells
この信号は 2 つの腐った独房から送信されます
you also know never enough
あなたも十分にはわかっていない
directly after ten years
10年後すぐに
they want to know what molecule
彼らはどの分子を知りたいのですか
So after 10 years they found
そこで10年後に彼らは発見した
ok let's see
わかりました、見てみましょう
In this case I put this
この場合はこれを入れます
They can since they are naked
裸だからできる
This ambrosex this matching capsule
このアンブロセックス、このお揃いのカプセル
We'll just separate all the cells out of it
すべてのセルを分離するだけです
cells in which we can
私たちができる細胞
All it can find is the synergy cell
見つけられるのはシナジーセルだけ
put this synergy cell
このシナジーセルを入れます
go inside it protein law
タンパク質の法則の中に入る
found a group of proteins
タンパク質のグループを発見した
This group of proteins is abundantly expressed
このグループのタンパク質は豊富に発現されます
Then it finds the gene
それから遺伝子を見つけます
then antibodies
それから抗体
It can be found that it is really
実際に存在していることがわかります。
ambrosex in the pig hole
豚の穴のアンブセックス
Then they did a cool
それから彼らはクールな作品を作りました
Is that the molecule
それは分子ですか
Really attracts pollen tubes to grow
本当に花粉管を引き寄せて成長する
really
本当
when you are cultivating people
人を育てるとき
you found click here
ここをクリックして見つけました
you can find the pollen tube
花粉管を見つけることができます
will reduce the growth in this place
この場所の成長を抑制します
So they found this
そこで彼らはこれを見つけました
defending like this protein
このタンパク質のように防御する
is involved in this thing
この事に関わっている
you can watch this grow
これが成長するのを見ることができます
you can watch this cool
これをクールに見ることができます
It turns when it taps the pollen tube
花粉管を叩くと回転する
click it here again
もう一度ここをクリックしてください
pollen tube turns
花粉管が曲がる
so you know something like this
だからあなたはこのようなことを知っていますか
it attracts pollen tubes
花粉管を引き寄せる
That is, guide the growth of pollen tubes
つまり、花粉管の成長を誘導する
so this is a very interesting
これはとても興味深いですね
so in this
それでこれで
This is under this tight this plant material
これはこの植物材料の下にあります
they just
彼らはただ
we just found this
私たちはちょうどこれを見つけました
Is there any other molecular wild material?
他に野生の分子物質はありますか?
Recently they also found
最近彼らも見つけました
Arab world has similar
アラブ世界にも同様のことがあります
but these
しかし、これら
In fact, what I want to tell you is a
実は、私が皆さんにお伝えしたいのは、
Just now that is a dicotyledonous plant
今のところ双子葉植物です
our monocots
私たちの単子葉植物
Iron Lily
アイアンリリー
iron lily this is a
アイアン・キャノン・リリー、これは
it has a hollow style
それは中空のスタイルを持っています
Then what
じゃあ何
We did an experiment
私たちは実験をしました
we just want to say
私たちはただ言いたいだけです
We hollow these styles
私たちはこれらのスタイルを空洞化します
Since we want to attract pollen tubes to grow
花粉管を引き寄せて成長させたいので
It should be these things in the style
スタイルではこれらのことである必要があります
should play an important role
重要な役割を果たすべきである
and we wanted to say
そして私たちが言いたかったのは
Pollen tubes grow a bit like animal cells
花粉管は動物細胞のように成長します
especially in this
特にこれでは
so-called hollow pool
所謂的中空的池
The hollow style
中空スタイル
it is an attachment
それは添付ファイルです
then grow on the move
その後、移動しながら成長します
you just saw
あなたは今見た
So we developed a way like this
そこで私たちはこのような方法を開発しました
We really found you this is Nitroceus Memes
本当に見つけました、ニトロセウス・ミームスです
This is an artificial membrane
これは人工膜です
When you coat this layer on the film
この層をフィルム上にコーティングすると、
When this star exits you take the pollen tube
この星が出るとき、あなたは花粉管を受け取ります
put the film on
フィルムを貼ります
You can find that the pollen tube seems to be
花粉管がこうなっているのがわかります。
It's like a big foot extended like this
大きな足をこうやって伸ばしたような感じです
And finally we want to say
そして最後に言いたいのは
Indicates the substance inside
中の物質を示します
Possibly attached to pollen
花粉に付着している可能性があります
and attract growth
そして成長を引き寄せる
So after I graduated
それで卒業してから
The teachers in my doctoral class will continue to have a Post-up
私の博士課程のクラスの先生たちは今後もポストアップを続ける予定です
he will remember
彼は覚えているだろう
From this, they use lust analysis
これから、彼らは欲望分析を使用します
A substance is separated from it
物質がそこから分離される
You can find that when this substance
この物質が
what he did was very
彼がしたことはとても素晴らしいことだった
That girl's eyes are really amazing
あの女の子の目は本当に素晴らしいです
he's on this slope
彼はこの坂の上にいる
Then dig a hole in the middle of this thing
それからこのものの真ん中に穴を掘ってください
you put that thing you can put in
入れられるものを入れます
you are variously purified
あなたはいろいろと浄化されます
Different Purified Things
さまざまな浄化されたもの
Then you take the pollen grains
それから花粉粒を摂取します
The benefits of Iron Cannon Lily are
アイアン・キャノン・リリーの利点は次のとおりです。
Its pollen grains are super large
花粉の粒子が超大きい
it's super big
超大きいです
you can see it with meat
肉を見ればわかります
Then it circles around the outside
それから外側を一周します
so that the pollen tube germination is all facing outward
花粉管の発芽がすべて外側を向くようにする
pick slowly with a needle
針でゆっくりと摘む
If today this material
今日この資料なら
can attract pollen tubes
花粉管を引き寄せることができる
It will grow outward and grow in again
それは外側に成長し、また内側に成長します
if it is water
それが水であれば
it will grow wildly
それは激しく成長するだろう
So later it found
それで後で見つけました
really this thing
本当にこれ
it affects it
それはそれに影響を与える
and it's a protein
そしてそれはプロテインです
When you, the stored substance
保存されている物質が
after you add
追加した後
lost activity
失われた活動
Finally they found a
ついに彼らは、
Cymocyanin
シモシアニン
it's a protein
それはタンパク質です
So that means
つまり、
possibly among different species
おそらく異なる種の間で
have different molecules
異なる分子を持っている
or protein
またはプロテイン
participate in this mechanism
この仕組みに参加する
So I think this is a
それで私はこれはだと思います
That means we're in the middle of the process
つまり、私たちはプロセスの途中にいるということです
Now of course one after another
もちろん次から次へと
students now
今の学生
their laboratory
彼らの研究室
they talk
彼らは話します
ok we now know
わかりました、もうわかりました
There is a general definition of Micropile
マイクロパイルには一般的な定義があります
What is the general definition of Funical?
Funical の一般的な定義は何ですか?
the other pollen tube
もう一方の花粉管
to go all the way down from the casting head
キャスティングヘッドからずっと下まで行く
What is this long-distance signal?
この長距離信号は何ですか?
So scientists are never satisfied
だから科学者たちは決して満足しない
So they also try to
そこで彼らはまた、
I heard that I found it
見つけたと聞きました
but not yet published
しかしまだ出版されていない
We'd like to say that we'll probably know soon
おそらくすぐにわかるだろうと言いたいのですが
What molecules are attracted to this petal jar?
この花びらの壺にはどのような分子が引き寄せられるのでしょうか?
All the way from the casting head along the style
キャスティングヘッドからスタイルに沿ってずっと
finally to the fat
ついに脂肪に
Embryo pig
胚豚
its growth
その成長
so it's a process
それはプロセスです
The next thing I want to tell you is that we have been here for about ten years
次にお伝えしたいのは、私たちがここに来て約10年になるということです
Twenty or ten years
20年か10年
Ten years?
10年？
should be about the same
ほぼ同じはずです
I do Post-Auto there
そこでポストオートをやります
about ten years
約10年
I'm sorry for twenty years
二十年間ごめんなさい
some recent tools
最近のツール
For example, we have long believed that
たとえば、私たちは長い間こう信じてきました。
You want to see the finer structure of the cell
細胞のより細かい構造を見たい
You're going to the electron microscope
電子顕微鏡に行きます
electron microscope
電子顕微鏡
right
右
The light microscope has its one limit
光学顕微鏡には限界が 1 つあります
but in the past this
しかし過去にはこれ
In addition to a research and development of optical microscopes in recent years
近年では光学顕微鏡の研究開発に加え、
There is also the root of a technology called the digital camera
いわゆるデジタルカメラの技術も根付いています。
We have something called a confocal optical microscope
共焦点光学顕微鏡というものがあります
This makes the optical microscope
これにより光学顕微鏡が作られます。
FusionExcel's optical microscope seems to be reborn again
FusionExcelの光学顕微鏡がまた生まれ変わるそうです
an opportunity for regeneration
再生の機会
The other one is that we now have really good computers
もう 1 つは、今では非常に優れたコンピューターがあることです。
works fast enough
十分に速く動作します
It is possible to process these images
このような画像を加工することも可能です
Then there are some fluorescent proteins
それからいくつかの蛍光タンパク質があります
Production of fluorescent substances
蛍光体の製造
Finally there is a laser system
ついにレーザーシステムが登場
These three
この３つ
These four things finally make a
この 4 つによって最終的には
We now have what's called a confocal microscope
今では共焦点顕微鏡と呼ばれるものがあります。
Many research institutes now have
現在、多くの研究機関は、
What is the so-called confocal microscope
いわゆる共焦点顕微鏡とは何ですか
Our Traditional Fluorescence Microscope
当社の伝統的な蛍光顕微鏡
its light source
その光源
The message we received was like this
届いたメッセージはこんな感じでした
but conjugate focus
しかし共役焦点
It can be said that it can use a computer to see
コンピュータを使って見ることができると言えます。
so you can put your laser
レーザーを入れることができます
only on a certain layer
特定の層のみ
it's yours it's yours
それはあなたのものです、それはあなたのものです
This is your specimen of your plant
これはあなたの植物の標本です
You can only position in this collar
この首輪でのみ位置決めできます
or locate here
またはここにあります
you put other noise signals
他のノイズ信号を入れると
Use Filter to filter it out
フィルタを使用して除外します
So what effect does it have
では、どのような効果があるのでしょうか
This is the tradition we see
これが私たちが見ている伝統です
Conventional Fluorescence Microscopy
従来の蛍光顕微鏡
but you can see
しかし、あなたは見ることができます
concord microscope
コンコード顕微鏡
Can make your image see more clearly
画像をより鮮明に見ることができます
Your image can be seen more clearly
画像がより鮮明に見えるようになります
For example, we can in this
たとえば、これでできることは、
You can see us using
私たちが使っているのを見ることができます
It can be at different delivery locations
配送場所が異なる場合があります
We can scan a pollen tube
花粉管をスキャンできる
top to bottom
上から下へ
you can go from top to bottom
上から下まで行くことができます
Finally, you can use the computer to combine
最後に、コンピューターを使用して組み合わせることができます。
a 3D construct
一個3D的構造
for example
例えば
This is an air port that our lab is working on
これは私たちの研究室が取り組んでいる空港です
it's arabian
それはアラビアです
arabian world you can find
あなたが見つけることができるアラビアンワールド
Scanning TV mirrors seem to look like
テレビミラーをスキャンすると次のようになります
Give you cool 3D
クールな 3D を提供します
A bit of a 3D effect, right?
ちょっとした3D効果ですよね？
This we also see the fluorescent representative
これには蛍光の代表も見られます
How can the effect of generating electricity
発電するとどのような効果が得られるのか
but
しかし
You use
あなたが使う
Very focal effect
非常に焦点効果が高い
what effect can you give
どのような効果を与えることができますか
you can see
見ることができます
you can scan
スキャンできます
you can swipe from top to bottom
上から下にスワイプできます
You can see that this is a stomata structure
これが気孔構造であることがわかります
You can make the pores have a three-dimensional structure like this
このように毛穴を立体的な構造にすることができます
This is from top to bottom
これは上から下まで
It's okay if you're not satisfied
満足できなくても大丈夫です
we can go from left to right
左から右へ行くことができます
you can see this blowhole
この噴気孔が見えます
These are two air pockets
これは2つのエアポケットです
Then there is a hole in the middle
そうすると真ん中に穴が空いてます
where the gas can freely pass through
ガスが自由に通過できる場所
you can side
あなたは側に立つことができます
A microscope made like this from the side
顕微鏡を横から見るとこんな感じ
So this can be used quite a bit
これならかなり使えますよ
It's okay if you don't think it's enough
足りないと思っても大丈夫
We can do 3D
3Dもできるよ
You can use different
さまざまな使い方ができます
You can make structures in 3D
3Dで構造物を作ることができる
So you can combine it with
したがって、次のものと組み合わせることができます
you can scan different
さまざまなスキャンができます
You combine all the images of this thing
このもののすべての画像を組み合わせます
you can watch
あなたは見ることができます
so you can see
それでわかります
If your protein special Label is in a certain pair
タンパク質の特別なラベルが特定のペアにある場合
You can see your protein in
タンパク質を確認できます
this cell
この細胞
or a particular location inside the cell
またはセル内の特定の場所
So you can push the function to heat it
したがって、機能を押して加熱することができます
So this is a pretty interesting
これはかなり興味深いですね
conventional microscope
従来の顕微鏡
We can see that
それがわかります
or by silver cursor
または銀色のカーソルで
or elevator microscope
またはエレベーター顕微鏡
you can tell
教えてもいいよ
This seems to look fine detail
これは細部まで細かく見えます
but what
でも何
They are all dead cells
それらはすべて死んだ細胞です
they are all
彼らは全員です
you will want to say
と言いたくなるでしょう
So what would it be like under the living body?
では、生体の下ではどうなっているのでしょうか？
So by one like this
それで、このようなものによって
So finally one of the things we found was
それで、最終的に私たちが見つけたものの1つは、
silver light protein
シルバーライトプロテイン
i think everyone knows
誰もが知っていると思います
We have a lot of news from before the network
ネットワーク化以前からのニュースがたくさんあります
silver light fish zebrafish
シルバーライトフィッシュゼブラフィッシュ
all kinds
すべての種類
It is mainly a silver light protein
主にシルバーライトタンパク質です
I used to find green
よく緑を見つけた
red now
今は赤い
various colors
さまざまな色
when your color
あなたの色のとき
When you are the appearance of silver light protein
シルバーライトプロテインの出現時
you can find
発見できる
assortment you can use on animals
動物に使用できる品揃え
can be used on plants
植物に使用できます
how it is used in plants
植物でどのように使われるか
For example, we can use the protein
たとえば、タンパク質を使用できます。
Although we see stomata
気孔は見えていますが
ovules you see
胚珠が見えます
This is the whole embryo
これが胚全体です
This is the middle of the process of cell division we see
これは私たちが見ている細胞分裂のプロセスの途中です
A variation of imitation hammer wire
模造ハンマーワイヤーのバリエーション
or inside a plant leaf that we can get
または私たちが入手できる植物の葉の中
do so-called Potoplas
いわゆるポトプラをする
Then we can do some analysis
それから、いくつかの分析を行うことができます
Ours is, for example, this is
私たちのものは、たとえばこれです
This is the chloroplast
これが葉緑体です
we can do many many things
私たちはたくさんのことができる
others you can see
あなたが見ることができる他のもの
like a cytoskeleton
細胞骨格のように
Cytoskeleton Sidere Scalata
細胞骨格シデレ スカラタ
You can find this is
これは見つかります
This is the fresh hair on the surface of the leaf
これは葉の表面に生えている生毛です。
you can see these cytoskeletons
これらの細胞骨格を見ることができます
how do you form such a construct
どうやってそのような構造を形成しますか
the one we just talked about
私たちが今話したもの
Can see Live Image
ライブ映像が見られる
This is a Live Image
これはライブ画像です
You can see that its Label is imitation hammer wire
ラベルが模造ハンマーワイヤーであることがわかります。
Microtubule
微小管
you can find
発見できる
you see the cells are dividing
細胞が分裂しているのがわかります
you can see
見ることができます
right in front of your eyes
あなたの目の前で
you can see living cells
生きた細胞を見ることができます
Live Whole Your Gene Bomber
Live Whole Your Gene Bomber
the whole change
全体の変化
Although I think it's a
だと思いますが、
for us is a
私たちにとっては
very useful tool
非常に便利なツール
Is it useful?
役に立ちますか?
So we are now saying
そこで私たちは今こう言っています
Both these tools
これらのツールはどちらも
what we couldn't do before
以前はできなかったこと
For example, before we could only say
たとえば、以前はこうしか言えなかったのですが、
whip out a protein or something
プロテインか何かを泡立てます
Now you can use fluorescent subtraction to mirror
蛍光減算を使用してミラーリングできるようになりました。
we use some way to turn straight
いくつかのターンストレートを使用します
We can see these cells in living
私たちはこれらの細胞を生きたまま見ることができます
even you can see the little cytoplasm
小さな細胞質さえ見えます
Inside the Cytoskeleton of Matter Research
物質研究の細胞骨格の内部
running in and out
出たり入ったり
wait till we have one
できるまで待ってください
A video to introduce to you
ご紹介する動画です
Then our laboratory research is mainly
それでは、私たちの研究室の研究は主に
Some genes involved in the sexual biomass of plants
植物の有性バイオマスに関与するいくつかの遺伝子
Same
同じ
This is the life of the whole plant
これは植物全体の命です
Our main thing is
私たちの主なことは
The earliest our laboratory
私たちの研究室の最も早い時期
I'm personally interested in pollen
個人的に花粉に興味がある
Because I think pollen is really a
花粉は本当にあると思うから
very cool
とてもかっこいい
Why
なぜ
it is a cell
それは細胞です
it has its own cell box
専用のセルボックスがあります
we call nutrition box
私たちは栄養ボックスと呼んでいます
But inside this cell
でもこの細胞の中では
two more gold cells
さらに2つのゴールドセル
So it is an extremely degenerate
だからそれは非常に退廃的なものです
a bear configuration
クマの構成
but it's a cell box
でもそれはセルボックスです
so it can be done
だからそれはできる
Pretty good for a cytology
細胞診としてはかなり良い
study one
一つ勉強してください
Then in the past and later, in the past few years in the future, we will slowly expand
そして、これまでも、そしてこれからも、そしてここ数年、そしてこれからも、ゆっくりと拡大していきます。
We found that some of the research we did started to lead to the so-called configuration
私たちが行った調査の一部は、いわゆる構成につながることがわかりました。
The development of the male and female gametes
雄と雌の配偶子の発達
In the end, we also found that something to do with the seeds
最終的には、種子と関係があることもわかりました。
So we all revolve around the reproductive growth of so-called plants
つまり、私たちは皆、いわゆる植物の生殖成長を中心に展開しています
For the past few years we have used
過去数年間、私たちが使用してきたのは、
We want to be able to study certain genes or proteins
特定の遺伝子やタンパク質を研究できるようにしたい
How to participate in so-called male gametes or pollination
いわゆる雄の配偶子または受粉に参加する方法
or the process of so-called embryonic development
またはいわゆる胚発生のプロセス
We used iron cannon lily rice and Arabian circles as materials
素材には鉄砲百合米とアラビアンサークルを使用しました
But let me introduce to you today
でも今日は紹介させてください
We have spent the past few years in Iron Cannon Lily
私たちはここ数年をアイアン・キャノン・リリーで過ごしてきました
Iron Lily
アイアンリリー
Why did we use Iron Cannon Lily in the first place?
そもそもなぜアイアン・キャノン・リリーを使用したのでしょうか？
You go and see
あなたは行って見ます
This is the anther of the iron cannon lily
これはアイアンキャノンリリーの葯です
The small and pitiful one next to it is the flower of the Arabian world
その隣の小さくて可哀そうなのはアラビア世界の花です
You can find that its anthers are much larger than other people's flowers
葯が他の人の花よりもかなり大きいことがわかります。
It's certainly a good material
確かに良い素材ですね
Another one you can find
あなたが見つけられるもう一つの
it is a hollow style
中空スタイルです
There are ways to collect so-called
いわゆる集める方法があります
Pollen House at Invival
インバイバルの花粉ハウス
The third we found
3番目に見つけたのは
its stigma
その汚名
it constantly secretes a
常に分泌している
sticky sticky stuff
粘着性の粘着物
Our name is Stella Exde
私たちの名前はステラ・エクスデです
You can find this sticky down
この粘着性のあるダウンを見つけることができます
we can collect this
私たちはこれを集めることができます
we can find out
私たちは知ることができます
Later this Stella Exde is very magical
あと、このステラエクスデはとても魔法です
it has something in it
それには何かが入っている
When your pollen is placed at minus 20 degrees
花粉がマイナス20度に置かれた場合
saved for 6 months
6か月間保存されました
Then you stop normally and take it out
あとは普通に止まって取り出す
The efficiency of the pollen hall is very poor
花粉ホールの効率が非常に悪い
right? think about it
そうでしょう？考えてみましょう
Don't talk about people
人のことを話すな
Pollen House, right?
花粉館對不對
like a cell
細胞のように
pollen grain
花粉粒
But pollen like you
でも、あなたと同じように花粉が
stored pollen
蓄積された花粉
You add Stella Exde
ステラエクスデを追加します
About 10% Stella Exde
ステラエクスデ 約10%
It restores the germination of pollen tubes
花粉管の発芽を回復します
So it's kind of like a rejuvenation effect
若返り効果みたいなものですね
so our laboratory
それで私たちの研究室
interested in this too
これにも興味があります
We Later We Now Lab
We Later We Now Lab
We draw this Stella Exde
このステラエクスデを描きます
We want to be able to Purify its molecule
分子を精製できるようにしたい
So we use the so-called
そこで、いわゆる
Chromatic Analysis
色成分析法
We have divided into different Fraction
さまざまな分数に分かれています
And one of the ones we found now
そして今見つけたものの一つは
These two freshers very much retain such activity
この 2 人の新人は、そのような活動を非常に維持しています
And the molecules are now probably identified as well.
そしておそらく分子も同定されたと思われます。
just don't know what it is
それが何なのかわからないだけです
Its three-dimensional 3D structure is left-handed and right-handed
その立体的な3D構造は左巻きと右巻きです。
Or does this molecule have other derivatives?
それとも、この分子には他の誘導体があるのでしょうか?
We look a bit like a derivative of ancetonic acid
私たちはアンセリン酸の誘導体に少し似ています
But now we have to go further
しかし今はさらに前進しなければなりません
Hope to be able to synthesize to test
合成してテストできるといいですね
so this is where we are
ここが私たちのいる場所です
Because the pollen house I just talked about
だって、さっき話した花粉の家が
You see, the pollen hall can be used as
ほら、花粉ホールは次のように使えます。
basically what happens inside a cell
基本的に細胞内で何が起こっているのか
So the message goes
それでメッセージはこうなります
Cap ion goes in
キャップイオンが入ります
All of these are on the pollen pavilion
これらはすべて花粉館にあります
so it is a very good as a material
素材としてはとても良いです
So let's say we have two graduate students
大学院生が 2 人いるとします。
high school student
高校生
high school students they will one day
高校生、彼らはいつかそうなるだろう
They come to our laboratory
彼らは私たちの研究室に来ます
He said he wanted to do a science exhibition, and I said yes.
彼は科学展示会をやりたいと言いました、そして私はそう言いました。
what do you want to do
何をしたいですか
I want to say this is good for them to do
彼らがそうするのは良いことだと言いたい
you can find them found to do
あなたは彼らがやるべきことを見つけることができます
Finally, it was found that when the pollen tubes are in the middle of the process
最後に、花粉管がそのプロセスの途中にあるとき、
What happens to the oil in it
中の油はどうなるのでしょうか
changes in oil
オイルの変化
Later in fact we were before
後になって、実際には私たちは以前はそうでした
A few years ago we discovered that in plants
数年前、私たちは植物でそれを発見しました
We can use Iron Cannon Lily
アイアンキャノンリリィも使えるよ
Although it is an iron cannon lily, although it cannot be genetically modified
アイアンキャノンリリーですが、遺伝子組み換えは出来ませんが、
But scientists are still very powerful
しかし、科学者は依然として非常に強力です
gene gun
遺伝子銃
We take the proteins we find
私たちは見つけたタンパク質を摂取します
Then we code on an energy
次に、エネルギーをコーディングします
like say this is us
これが私たちだと言うように
Not sorry
申し訳ありません
plasticizing
可塑化
a plastid
一個質體
have the genes we want
私たちが望む遺伝子を持っている
Then we use the gene gun
それから遺伝子銃を使います
Hit this gene until after this
この遺伝子をこの後までヒットさせてください
Let's use comfoca to see
comfocaを使って見てみましょう
so you can find
だからあなたは見つけることができます
iron lily
アイアンリリー
you can find
発見できる
This protein can really express
このタンパク質は本当に表現できる
Then we have this one on the oil body
それなら私たちは石油体です
Purified protein
精製タンパク質
you can find
発見できる
As the pollen tube grows
花粉管が伸びるにつれて
You can find these oil bodies
これらの油体を見つけることができます
really works constantly
本当に常に動作します
so we know real pollen tubes
それで私たちは本物の花粉管を知っています
at least we
少なくとも私たちは
Later experiments also found
その後の実験でも発見された
When the whole pollen hall is covered
花粉ホール全体を覆うと
There is a group of fats that change
変化する脂肪のグループがあります
Another group of fat will increase
別のグループの脂肪が増加します
May be involved in cell membrane growth
細胞膜の成長に関与している可能性がある
Because the pollen hall grows it needs the cell membrane
花粉殿が成長するには細胞膜が必要です
Constant supply of cell membrane
細胞膜の継続的な供給
those material
それらの材料
So that might be the mechanism
そういうメカニズムなのかもしれない
So we're in the middle of the process
つまり、私たちはプロセスの途中にいるのです
we also found a
私たちも見つけました
a so-called cytoskeletal protein
いわゆる細胞骨格タンパク質
It's called LIM
リムといいます
Then we also did some experiments
それから私たちはいくつかの実験も行いました
What are cytoskeletal proteins?
細胞骨格タンパク質とは何ですか?
it's a cartoon
それは漫画です
you can find
発見できる
this is the root of a plant
これは植物の根です
Then they made genetically modified plants
それから彼らは遺伝子組み換え植物を作りました
He found that this protein only had GFG fluorescence
彼は、このタンパク質が GFG 蛍光のみを持っていることを発見しました。
You can find it manifesting in root hairs
根毛に現れていることがわかります
You see and then they order
見て、彼らは注文します
it's all real
それはすべて本当です
The words below the back are cartoons
後ろの下の文字は漫画です
that's what they found
それが彼らが見つけたものです
This is a cytoskeletal protein
これは細胞骨格タンパク質です
It should help you out of the so-called
それはいわゆる問題からあなたを助けるはずです
Acting Weiss's A Knot
ワイスの「結び目」を演じる
What is the structure of these micro divisions that you finally found out
ついにわかったミクロの区画の構造とは
it's...you can find it walking around
それは...歩き回っていると見つかります
It's these proteins it's an acid binding protein
これらのタンパク質は酸結合タンパク質です
it has a nonspecies species on it
そこには非種の種が含まれています
You can find it can walk up and down on this
この上を上り下りできることがわかります
So it's fun. This is the Western Gaogu religion.
楽しいですね、ここは西高古代教会です。
This is Sytle skeleton
こちらはスタイルスケルトン
The thing we make doesn't go like this
私たちが作るものはこのようにはいきません
but also something like
しかし、次のようなものもあります
So for example we find
たとえば、次のようになります。
when normal in this pollen house
この花粉の家では通常の場合
We still use the gene gun to express
私たちは表現するために今でも遺伝子銃を使用しています
You can find our protein
当社のプロテインを見つけることができます
it will follow the cytoskeleton
それは細胞骨格に従います
It's F acting, it's the combination of micro-teachers
それはFの演技、それはマイクロ教師の組み合わせです
But when you're dealing with this micro division's decomposing matter
しかし、このミクロな分裂の腐敗する物質を扱っているときは、
You can find that the combination is gone
組み合わせがなくなっていることがわかります
Then when we do a lot of this performance
それで、このパフォーマンスをたくさんやるとき、
you see it found
見つかりましたね
When pollen tubes are abundant
花粉管が豊富な時期
Originally normal growth pollen tube
本来は正常に成長する花粉管
You will find that there is a middle pollen tube
真ん中に花粉管があるのがわかります。
There will be a joint-like thing appearing at the tip
先端に関節のようなものが現れます
Let's say you're like a normal pollen tube
あなたが通常の花粉管のようなものだとしましょう
it grows like this
このように成長します
it will keep growing
それは成長し続けるだろう
But when your gene happens
しかし、あなたの遺伝子が起こると、
When you let this protein express in large quantities
このタンパク質を大量に発現させると
Pollen tube growth stops
花粉管の成長が止まる
Then you can find that the pollen tubes grow
すると花粉管が伸びていくのがわかります
In the middle of this process, there is a particularly bright
このプロセスの途中で、特に明るいことがあります。
Our protein creates a
私たちのタンパク質は、
a so-called aggregation of thinking
いわゆる思考の集合体
This will affect the pollen tube
花粉管に影響を及ぼします
It will prevent the pollen tube from continuing to grow.
花粉管が成長し続けるのを防ぎます。
So use this way
だからこのように使ってください
we just know
私たちはただ知っています
Our protein may be a Wisdom-binding protein
私たちのタンパク質は、知恵を結合するタンパク質である可能性があります
it for it throughout the pollen tube
花粉管全体に渡って
It must go through the growth process
成長過程を経る必要がある
very fine regulation
非常に細かい規制
so this is a
これは
Another one we just talked about
先ほど話したもう一つのこと
A pollination of whole pollen
全花粉の受粉
we want to know
私たちは知りたい
How does pollen grow in the word dimension
花粉はワード次元でどのように成長するのか
Because all of our current literature above
なぜなら、上記の現在の文献はすべて
All of us, like what we just said
私たち全員、今言ったことのように
The Arab world has a lot of information on the Internet
アラブ世界にはインターネット上に多くの情報があります
These are all from the incubator
これらはすべて保育器からのものです
growing pollen hall
成長する花粉ホール
then we were thinking
それから私たちは考えていました
The pollen hall grows inside the style
花柱の内側に花粉ホールが生える
why you can find out
なぜ知ることができるのか
We grow in in vitro culture machine
体外培養機で生育する
and internally grown pollen pavilions
自家栽培の花粉パビリオン
The first pollen pavilion grown inside the body
体内で増殖した初の花粉パビリオン
grow very fast
とても早く成長します
Iron Lily
アイアンリリー
its from stigma to style to its fat
汚名からスタイル、脂肪まで
The middle can be up to about 15 cm
真ん中は15cmくらいまであります
It can grow from head to tail in two days
2日で頭から尻尾まで成長する
But the incubator you grow in vitro
しかし、あなたが体外で育てるインキュベーター
never last that long
そんなに長くは続かない
can't grow so fast
そんなに早く成長できない
The other one is in Iron Explosion Lily
もう1つは鉄爆リリーにあります
we can find out
私たちは知ることができます
growing in the stylet
スタイレットで成長する
it attaches to each other
それは互いにくっついている
Not only attached to each other
お互いにくっつくだけじゃなくて
will also be tightly attached to the so-called
いわゆる
emits a surface of this layer
このレイヤーの表面を放出します
a cell called the epidermal
表皮と呼ばれる細胞
so we were thinking
それで私たちは考えていました
Is it growing in vitro or in vivo?
それはインビトロで成長していますか?それともインビボで成長していますか?
the only difference
唯一の違い
Teeth
歯
Is it the one played by Gary?
ゲイリーが演じた人ですか？
what kind of role
どのような役割ですか
because of some materials
一部の素材のせいで
so there's been no way anyone would know
だから誰も知る方法はなかった
these pollen tubes
この花粉管
what's going on in the body
体の中で何が起こっているのか
so a few years ago
それで数年前に
we used a special method
私たちは特別な方法を使いました
let's just let this
これだけにしておきましょう
We constructed a transplant pig material
移植用豚材料を構築しました
It uses pollen-specific proteins
花粉特有のタンパク質を使用
received a call
電話を受けた
ribosomal protein
リボソームタンパク質
Ribosomes, do you remember?
リボソーム、覚えていますか?
At first, what I just said earlier
まず、先ほども言いましたが、
from genes not most
ほとんどの遺伝子からではない
what messenger to use
どのメッセンジャーを使用するか
message messenger
メッセージメッセンジャー
from the nucleus to the cytoplasm
核から細胞質まで
ribosome
リボソーム
final protein
最終タンパク質
the ribosomal protein
リボソームタンパク質
So we put this protein
そこでこのプロテインを入れます
how about after showing
見せた後はどうですか？
Because if you think about it, all the genes are going to come from
なぜなら、考えてみれば、すべての遺伝子は由来することになるからです。
Gene to Messenger
遺伝子からメッセンジャーへ
Messenger ends up in the ribosome
メッセンジャーは最終的にリボソームに到達する
So of course we our
だからもちろん私たちも
When ribosomes can be labeled
リボソームを標識できる場合
Let's use Country again
もう一度カントリーを使ってみよう
This ribosome can contain the incoming
このリボソームには、入ってくる
The message RNA precipitates it all together
RNA というメッセージがすべてを沈殿させます
At this time we use this way
今回はこの方法を使います
What we can find is inside the style
私たちが見つけられるのはスタイルの中にあります
protein inside growing pollen tube
成長中の花粉管内のタンパク質
And with a so-called
そして、いわゆる
Non-destructive we have something called Translator
非破壊的なTranslatorと呼ばれるものがあります
That is to say, some of the message RNA
つまり、RNA のメッセージの一部は、
inside the pollen tube
花粉管の中
A message inside a growing pollen tube
伸びる花粉管の中のメッセージ
this we can find
これは私たちが見つけることができます
what kind of protein
どのようなタンパク質ですか
Which gene products of this process
このプロセスのどの遺伝子産物か
Also we can find
また、私たちは見つけることができます
This gene is really fun
この遺伝子は本当に面白いです
This is normal Wildtide
これが通常のワイルドタイドです
you can spot a pollen tube
花粉管を見つけることができます
Will only meet from a micro
マイクロからのみ会います
But when you some
しかし、あなたがいくつかのとき
We find these genes
私たちはこれらの遺伝子を見つけます
to find its mutant
その変異株の発見を目指して
its pollen tube
その花粉管
The first pig's mouth that couldn't find Chi Rui
チ・ルイを見つけられなかった最初の豚の口
or that it will pass through
あるいは通過するだろうということ
additional or multiple pollen tubes
追加または複数の花粉管
So this is basically
したがって、これは基本的には
when these are in the pollen
これらが花粉の中にあるとき
gene generation
遺伝子の生成
when mutation
突然変異のとき
The whole behavior of your pollen tubes
花粉管の全体的な挙動
changed
かわった
another one
もう一つ
A student from one of our most recent labs
私たちの最近の研究室の学生
what he does is
彼がやっていることは
we found so many
私たちはたくさん見つけました
one of them
それらの中の一つ
this gene
この遺伝子
it is involved as well
それも関わってくる
Related to Raboson synthesis
ラボソン合成関連
But when your gene mutates
しかし、遺伝子が突然変異すると、
You can discover the structure of the entire pollen tube
花粉管全体の構造がわかる
The structure of this cell currency
このセル通貨の仕組み
or the inner cytoskeleton
または内部細胞骨格
have changed
変更されました
Finally, I would like to introduce to you a
最後にご紹介したいのは、
gene transfer technology
遺伝子組み換え技術
We just talked about TDNA
先ほどTDNAについてお話しました
This is what we rely on, Mr. Ermin
私たちが頼りにしているのはこれです、エルミンさん
he is the expert
彼は専門家です
Actually I don't really understand
実はよく分かりません
If you really want to change jobs on this
本気で転職したいなら
go to him
彼のところへ行く
He must give you a very perfect answer
彼はあなたにとても完璧な答えをくれるはずです
But what kind of sex is this
しかし、これはどういうセックスですか
That is to say, we are in the plant of Agrobacterium
つまり、私たちはアグロバクテリウムの工場にいるのです。
this pathogen
この病原体
We found out that it has something called TiPlasma
TiPlasmaと呼ばれるものがあることがわかりました
plastid
色素体
This thing is very special
これはとても特別なことです
We can do something on it
何かできるだろう
do something
何かをする
This TiPlasma will eventually
このTiPlasmaは最終的には
pinch pinch see first come
ピンチピンチ参照先着
will be delivered to the plant
工場に納品されます
Then look inside the genes of the plants first
次に、まず植物の遺伝子の内部を調べます
top of gene body
遺伝子本体の上部
will then result in a
その結果、
It can make it grow and mutate
それはそれを成長させ、突然変異させることができます
can also
こともできます
Sew in
縫い込む
Can cause a certain gene in the plant to be destroyed
植物の特定の遺伝子を破壊する可能性がある
so we talk
それで話します
The TiPlasma mutant just mentioned
先ほど言及した TiPlasma 変異体
Or you can make a gene
あるいは遺伝子を作ることもできる
massive performance
大量表現
This is one I found on the Internet
これはインターネットで見つけたものです
It is TiPlasma
ティプラズマです
You can put the gene you want
欲しい遺伝子を入れることができる
put in
入れます
then send it
それから送信します
In this so-called concentrated bacteria
このいわゆる濃縮バクテリアでは
Concentrated bacteria?
濃縮菌？
Then you can use it to infect plants
その後、それを使って植物に感染することができます
you can use it to infect plants
植物に感染するために使用できます
What about after you infect the plant?
植物に感染した後はどうなりますか？
this is a normal operation
これは通常の動作です
What about after infecting plants?
植物に感染した後はどうなるでしょうか？
This highly sensitive bacterium will use a special structure
この非常に感受性の高い細菌は特殊な構造を採用しています
will put the so-called TiPlasma
いわゆるTiPlasmaを入れます
into the plant
工場の中へ
well you get infected
まあ、あなたも感染しますよ
The Ecopter is attached to the cell wall of this plant
エコプターはこの植物の細胞壁に付着しています
when it attaches to the plant cell wall
植物の細胞壁に付着すると
What about this TiPlasma?
このティプラズマはどうでしょうか？
it enters the cell
それは細胞に入ります
then run to the cell wall
それから細胞壁に行きます
Then the whole of your gene
そうすればあなたの遺伝子全体が
with this thing it carries
それが運ぶこの物で
You can shoot first in the whole gene's
遺伝子全体を最初に撃つことができる
TiTiA will pick up here
TiTiAがここで迎えに来ます
entire
全体
so you can make genes
それで遺伝子を作ることができる
Genetic
遺伝的
a destruction of
の破壊
So you might be causing what's called a mutation
つまり、いわゆる突然変異を引き起こしている可能性があります
then you end up
それであなたは終わります
Previous words could be generated using
前の単語は次のように生成できます。
tissue culture
組織培養
Then you from tissue culture can finally generate
その後、組織培養から最終的に生成することができます
Then your tissue culture
次に、組織培養
Your DNA has a
あなたの DNA には、
For example, the volition potion of sand herb potion
例えば、サンドハーブポーションの意志ポーション
when you spray sand
砂を噴霧していたとき
as long as you have a job change
転職する限り
it's anti-weed
砂雑草に強いです
so you know it
だからあなたはそれを知っています
in such a way
そのような方法で
we can do it at last
ついにそれができます
so we were a few years ago
だから私たちは数年前に
We have a way like this
こんな方法もありますよ
Let's go
さあ行こう
because in the Arab world it is a
なぜならアラブ世界ではそれが
There is a nice support library
素晴らしいサポートライブラリがあります
called DNA Library
DNAライブラリーと呼ばれる
let's go find
探しに行きましょう
At that time we were interested in saying
当時私たちはこう言うことに興味を持っていました
when your seed
あなたの種がいつ
when you chicken mutant pig
突然変異の豚を鶏にするとき
As long as it has no so-called homologous offspring
いわゆる相同子孫がいない限り
It only has Historzygone
ヒストジゴネしかない
That is to say, if its homologous descendants
つまり、その相同子孫が
when you plant
植えるとき
There are two DNA's in it
そこには2つのDNAが入っている
homologous offspring
相同子孫
What does the absence of this homologous offspring mean?
この相同子孫が存在しないことは何を意味するのでしょうか?
There will be a problem with your configuration body
構成本体に問題がある可能性があります
So you can't spawn poor people or plants
したがって、貧しい人々や植物を生み出すことはできません
or yours
またはあなたの
There is a problem with the entire embryonic development
胚の発育全体に問題がある
So we use a strategy like this
そこで私たちはこのような戦略を採用します
We found quite a few genes
かなりの数の遺伝子が見つかりました
it's basically
それは基本的にです
This is the development of the whole embryo
これは胚全体の発達です
we discover
私たちは発見します
Quite a few are related to embryonic development
かなりの数が胚の発生に関連しています
It's a normal spider
普通の蜘蛛です
you can find
発見できる
it will be ten weeks different
10週間違うだろう
But we take this gene
しかし、私たちはこの遺伝子を受け取ります
when a gene is mutated
遺伝子が突然変異すると
you can find
発見できる
It turned out to be the so-called WATER
それはいわゆる「WATER」であることが判明しました
is in the Hard stage
ハードステージに入っています
At this time it is basically
現時点では基本的には
There is a problem with the whole development
開発全体に問題がある
so we know that means
だから私たちはそれが意味することを知っています
say it in this way
このように言ってください
This gene is involved in
この遺伝子が関与しているのは、
throughout embryonic development
胚の発育全体を通して
a certain process
あるプロセス
we have been in the past
私たちは過去にいた
We probably found quite a few
おそらくかなりの数が見つかりました
You can find that it may be following
次のようなことがわかります
Embryo magnet development
胚磁石の開発
One related to cell division
細胞分裂に関係するもの
In addition or some of the cells
さらに、細胞の一部
or nuclear RNA metabolism
または核RNA代謝
e.g. RNA
例: RNA
Methanageal RNA to be produced
生成されるメタナジアルRNA
to go through so called some nuclei
いわゆるいくつかの核を通過する
Add a Polyase to the whole process
プロセス全体にポリアーゼを追加する
the process it participates in
参加するプロセス
What about the third one?
3番目はどうでしょうか？
is to affect the so-called
いわゆるものに影響を与えることです
Endome Memet trafficking
エンドメメメットの人身売買
For example, the cytoskeleton we just talked about
たとえば、先ほど話した細胞骨格のようなものです。
those proteins like this
このようなタンパク質
So we use the time in the past
だから私たちは過去の時間を使います
we are probably
私たちはおそらく
There is quite a bit of research
かなり研究が進んでいる
say we are here
私たちはここにいると言う
We can find that it is possible to
次のことが可能であることがわかります。
on the ribose base
リボースベースで
The brevity of that RNA or
その RNA の簡潔さ、または
nuclear human development
核による人類開発
or a
または
with these
これらと
Or Endome Memet trafficking
またはエンドメメメットの人身売買
When your gene discovers
あなたの遺伝子が発見されるとき
when mutation
突然変異のとき
You can find the whole different package
まったく異なるパッケージを見つけることができます
changes in growth
成長の変化
So probably this is our past
だからおそらくこれは私たちの過去です
we were
私たちはいた
We're mostly following the development of pollen
私たちは主に花粉の発生を追っています
then fertilized
その後受精した
And finally we now also follow
そしてついに私たちも従うようになりました
planting development
植栽開発
this is us in the past
これは過去の私たちです
During this time we mainly do
この時期に主にやることは、
Finally, I want to tell you that
最後にこれだけは言っておきたいのですが、
In basic research we often ask
基礎研究でよく聞かれるのが、
what's the use of you doing that
そんなことして何の役に立つの？
In fact, the Basic Research Institute
実は、基礎研究所は、
I feel like we are here today
今日はここにいるような気がする
professional research institute
専門研究所
should say
言うべきだ
I should thank professional institute
専門機関に感謝しなければなりません
give me a place to fulfill my dreams
私の夢を叶える場所を与えてください
i probably from college
私はおそらく大学出身です
until the Ph.D.
博士課程まで
I'm probably doing this basic research
おそらくこの基礎研究をしているのでしょう
But I think it's really a
しかし、それは本当にあると思います
very interesting one
とても興味深いもの
a subject
一個課題
then the second we are here
それから私たちがここにいる二番目に
I think I have another mission
別の使命があると思う
in this education
この教育では
we are in the middle of this process
私たちはこのプロセスの真っ最中です
We have trained a considerable number of doctoral students
私たちはこれまでにかなりの数の博士課程の学生を育ててきました
postdoctoral fellow
博士後
Or say we have bred
あるいは、私たちが育てたと言うか
PhD students
博士課程の学生
later returned to their country
その後自国に戻った
Costa Rica
コスタリカ
He is now an assistant professor
彼は今助教授です
We have a postdoctoral fellow at Pingtung University of Science and Technology
屏東科学技術大学には博士研究員がいます
We have a postdoc in the US
米国にポスドクがいます
find a politics professor
政治学の教授を見つける
These are a mission we are here
これらは私たちがここにいる使命です
so i think it is
だからそうだと思う
What is the role of industry
産業の役割とは何ですか
I want to eat is a good one
食べたいです 食べるのはいいですよ
Five Fingers Watermelon
ファイブフィンガースイカ
five fingers watermelon we use
私たちが使用するファイブフィンガースイカ
For example we can generate
たとえば、次のように生成できます。
pistil
めしべ
double generation
複代
triploid pistil
三倍体雌しべ
Then the male is diploid
すると雄は二倍体です
We ended up using pollen tubes
結局花粉管を使うことになった
when fertilized
受精したとき
cause the fruit to expand
果実を膨張させる
But the fruit
でも果物は
Seeds cannot be produced
種が生産できない
so what's the end result
それで、最終的な結果は何ですか
double silver
ダブルシルバー
Consumers do not need to repaint after eating
消費者は食後に塗り直す必要がない
don't paint that paper
その紙に色を塗らないでください
right
右
but you use
しかし、あなたは使用します
To buy this seed from a seed company
この種子を種子会社から購入するには
because it has no seeds
種がないから
You can't respond to the next generation
次世代に対応できない
so i want to say
だから私は言いたいです
While you're in the middle of this process
このプロセスの途中で
you understand
分かるでしょう
you have a chance like this
あなたにはこのようなチャンスがあります
like i just said
先ほど言ったように
You can produce these with flowers within flowers
花の中に花を入れて制作することもできます
I think that's what we know
それが私たちが知っていることだと思います
a cumulative
一個累積
One result we can have
私たちが得ることができる 1 つの結果
Finally I think I'd like to thank you
最後にお礼を言いたいと思います
is ours
私たちのものです
over the past few years
過去数年にわたり
This is the first few years
これが最初の数年です
then it's the two of us
それなら私たち二人です
mathematics student
数学の学生
These two high school students seem to win prizes at every science fair they attend
この 2 人の高校生は、参加するサイエンス フェアのたびに賞を受賞しているようです
Probably going well is to be able to represent Taiwan to participate in the international science and technology exhibition
おそらくうまくいけば、台湾を代表して国際科学技術展示会に参加できるでしょう。
And then here's our executive team
そしてこちらが私たちの経営陣です
Today I want to thank this Tingyu
今日はこのティンギュに感謝したいと思います
The three organizations he does today
彼が現在活動している 3 つの組織
He was the one who did the tissue training in the Shihu Lake
彼は石湖で組織トレーニングを行った人でした
And then here's our administrative team across the command post
そしてこちらが指揮所にいる管理チームです
Our Research Assistants
私たちのリサーチアシスタント
I don't think there are some
いくつかはないと思います
So we need supplies for the logistics force
したがって、兵站部隊への物資が必要です
Only then can we do some research ahead
そうして初めて、先の調査を行うことができます
And finally thanks to the Ministry of Science and Technology
そして最後に科学技術省に感謝します
And our Academia Sinica
そして私たちの中央研究院
Cheviso and this agricultural development center
Cheviso とこの農業開発センター
All of this is a financial subsidy for us
これらはすべて私たちへの財政的補助金です
i think i'll stop here for today
今日はここでやめておこうと思います
Fortunately, everyone didn't sleep too much.
幸いなことに、みんなあまり寝ませんでした。
Then I welcome you if you have any questions
それでは、何かご質問がございましたら、よろしくお願いいたします
Thanks
ありがとう
Well, we thank Dr. Zhao for a very good presentation
趙博士の素晴らしいプレゼンテーションに感謝します。
so we now open the question
それでは質問を始めます
Work hard everyone, the public album will mention it to him on April 1
みんな頑張って、4月1日の公開アルバムで彼に言及します
say yes we have a little gift for the speakers
はい、講演者にちょっとしたプレゼントがありますと言ってください
On the side of the question asked, Mr. Zhao still has
質問された側の趙氏はまだこう答えている。
still have
まだ持っています
Responsibilities of our position
私たちの立場の責任
There is an introduction to us above and our
上記に私たちの紹介があります。
Information from our Facebook page
Facebookページからの情報
Welcome everyone, ginseng can come
皆さんようこそ、高麗人参が来ます
good
良い
Excuse me, there are bear flowers and snake flowers
すみません、熊の花と蛇の花があります
So how did the source of what is called a false flower come from?
では、偽の花と呼ばれるものの源はどのようにして来たのでしょうか?
What
何
false flower
偽の花
Generally speaking, we
一般的に言えば、私たちは、
we have bisexual flowers
私たちには両性花があります
That is to say, this kind of flower has tooth stamen and bear stamen
つまり、この種の花には歯しべと熊しべがあるのです。
this is normal
これは正常です
There's a so-called bear stamen
いわゆるXiong Ruiがあります
holding bear example like corn
たとえばトウモロコシのようなクマを抱えている
its pistil is on top
雌しべが上についています
Its stamens are at the bottom
雄しべが一番下にあります
So this is two generations called unisexual flowers
つまりこれは二世代の花と呼ばれるものです
I'm not very clear about false flowers
造花についてはよくわかりません
So this is according to
したがって、これは次のとおりです
this is the same flower
これは同じ花です
it has a sex
それにはセックスがある
we call bisexual flowers
私たちは両性花と呼びます
If you want unisexual flowers
ユニセックスな花が欲しいなら
That is, Chi Wei and Xiong Wei are separated
つまり、チーウェイとシオンウェイは離れ離れになる
yes
はい
teacher sorry
先生ごめんなさい
Just now you mentioned that
今、あなたはそれを言いましたね
you used to take that pollen tube
あなたは花粉管を取っていました
Yes, the pollen tube grows by itself
そう、花粉管は自ら伸びるのです
it you cut it off
あなたがそれを切り取ったのですか
because we need sperm
精子が必要だから
a humid space
湿気の多い空間
in a humid environment
湿気の多い環境で
Yeah so I'll tell you which one are you talking about
はい、じゃあどっちのことを言っているのか教えてあげるね
Because what I just said
なぜなら、私が今言ったことは、
because when you said cut off
なぜならあなたが切ると言ったとき
I'm sending it will it dry?
送りますが乾きますか？
very good right
とても良いですね
I didn't speak very carefully just now
今あまり慎重に話さなかった
that means we are the first
それは私たちが最初であることを意味します
We're going to make pollen, lean powder about 24
24時くらいに花粉、リーンパウダーを作ります
about 12 hours to 24 hours
約12時間～24時間
maybe i know where it grows
たぶん私はそれがどこで育つか知っています
At this time, after you cut off
このとき、切った後、
you need to seal it up
それを封印する必要がある
Or paint with decorative bells to prevent moisture from evaporating
または、水分の蒸発を防ぐために装飾用のベルをペイントします。
this is what needs to be done
これがやらなければならないことです
but you just
でもあなたはただ
you don't care how much you cut
どれだけカットしても気にしない
as long as you can maintain
維持できる限り
because it is in the whole pollen hall
花粉ホール全体にあるので
grow in style
おしゃれに成長する
it keeps forming
それは形成され続けます
I was talking about Keris Pluck
ケリス・プラックについて話していました
it can be a totally pollen house
完全に花粉の家になる可能性があります
The most active place at the front
最前線で最も活躍する場所
seal it up completely
完全に密閉する
you just keep that place
あなたはただその場所を保つだけです
Don't destroy the whole pollen hall
花粉ホール全体を破壊しないでください
It can deliver two gold cells to embryonic pigs
2つの金細胞を胎児ブタに送達できる
complete double fertilization
完全な重複受精
so amazing
本当に素晴らしい
So it means it will
つまり、そうなるということです
it pollen house will know
それは花粉の家が知っているでしょう
will feel the pool class
プールの授業を感じるでしょう
Embryo sac
胚嚢
send a message like this
このようなメッセージを送信してください
to attract it to grow
それを引き寄せて成長させる
At once
すぐに
we just talked about emptiness
私たちは空虚について話したばかりです
like iron lily
鉄の百合のように
it belongs to the style of the stroke
それはストロークのスタイルに属します
It's actually filled with liquid
実は液体が詰まっているんです
we call it from
から呼び出します
Its front capital is divided into
その正面首都は次のように分かれています。
Our name is Standard Exte
私たちの名前はスタンダードエクステです
it keeps going from the bottom
それは底から続いていく
secrete something like this
このようなものを分泌します
still have this
これはまだ持っています
yes still
はい、まだ
But pollen tubes are actually fun
でも花粉管って実は楽しいんです
That means it's just been pollinated on the stigma
つまり柱頭に受粉しただけということですね
grow and grow into the style
成長してスタイルに合わせて成長する
for a while
しばらくの間
it needs its own nourishment
それ自体の栄養が必要です
So it's a pollen tube, you go straight to the inside
それは花粉管です、中を覗いてみてください
it has a lot of oil bodies
油分が多く含まれている
There is still a lot of Starch
でんぷんはまだたくさんあります
starch liquid
でんぷん液
But wait until it grows in the style for a while
でもスタイルが良くなるまでしばらく待ってください
it will be from
からになります
Sirac is here to absorb nutrients
シラクは栄養素を吸収するためにここにいます
yes
はい
in the video just now
たった今のビデオの中で
It says that the DNA is not there are four of that
DNAは4つではないと言われています
to combine?
結合します？
Then it itself will delete what it says it doesn't want
その後、それ自体が望まないものを削除します
So have you learned from this
それで、あなたはこのことから学びましたか
how does the plant itself go about removing
植物自体はどのように除去するのでしょうか
because we now have
なぜなら私たちは今持っているから
Is there any progress on this?
これに関して何か進展はありますか？
Is there any technology in this area?
この分野に何か技術はあるのでしょうか？
Our current results are as far as I know
私が知る限りの現在の結果は次のとおりです
Yes know we have a program called
はい、というプログラムがあることは知っています
A mechanism of splicing to do these donations
これらの寄付を行うためのスプライシングのメカニズム
if you are interested
もし興味があれば
We recently had a teacher named Tu Shilong in our Institute of Botany
最近、私たちの植物学研究所にトゥ・シロンという名前の先生が来ました
He posted an article on Plain cell last month
彼は先月プレインセルに関する記事を投稿しました
Just to tell you what this mechanism will affect
このメカニズムがどのような影響を与えるかを説明します
it may take to plants affected by light
光の影響を受けた植物に影響を与える可能性があります
will affect flowering
開花に影響します
This is an article from our recent teacher
これは最近の先生からの記事です
It is to do this so-called splicing mechanism
これはいわゆるスプライシングメカニズムを行うためのものです
If you have a chance, you can go and find out
機会があれば行って確認してみてはいかがでしょうか
Thanks
ありがとう
The two techniques I've heard are
私が聞いたテクニックは次の2つです
One is strong and the other is
片方は強くて、もう片方は
That female dragon feels like you have a body
その雌ドラゴンは体を持っているように感じます
into plant cells
植物細胞に
Is there any other way to create a picture group
画像グループを作成する他の方法はありますか
For example, the recent hot gene editing and the like
例えば最近話題の遺伝子編集など
Gene editing is right
遺伝子編集は正しい
yes
はい
This is a good mechanism
これは良い仕組みですね
It's a system that uses CRISPR
CRISPRを使ったシステムです
The so-called TDNA
いわゆるTDNA
What is the benefit of this system of insertion or CRISPR
この挿入システムまたは CRISPR の利点は何ですか
you know where you insert
どこに挿入するか知っていますか
Also we have a mutant technology called EMS
また、EMSと呼ばれる突然変異技術もあります。
You can treat something like this with the seeds from which it was planted
このようなものを、それが植えられた種子で扱うことができます
You can see that it might be breaking a certain clip of DNA
DNA の特定のクリップが壊れている可能性があることがわかります。
You can cause Point Mutation
点突然変異を引き起こす可能性があります
When you Point Mutation is you three
点突然変異を行うときは 3 人です
You alone decide on an amino acid
アミノ酸を決めるのはあなた自身です
You may be at the end after you put this Point Mutation mutation
この点突然変異を最後に置いた後かもしれません
it should keep doing it
それはやり続けるべきだ
it stops here
ここで止まります
so you gene it has no way to complete one to produce a complete
したがって、遺伝子には完全なものを生み出す方法がありません。
but this thing you
でも、これはあなた
We call it Mapping
私たちはそれをマッピングと呼んでいます
you don't know which gene
どの遺伝子かわかりません
backcross
バッククロス
But this can also be done
でもこれもできるんです
can also do
もできます
But that is to say, it is slower
しかし、つまり、速度が遅くなるということです
is this another one
これはもう一つですか
What you just said is also a way
あなたが今言ったことも一つの方法です
now there are quite a few
今ではかなりの数があります
A gene gun is basically just a
遺伝子銃は基本的に単なる
We are called Train Sink
私たちはトレインシンクと呼ばれています
not a stable offspring
安定した子孫ではない
it's just for a short time you're in a certain
あなたが特定の状態にいるのはほんの短い間だけです
For example, today
たとえば、今日
In addition, what we just said is called
さらに、私たちが今言ったことは、
we can work
私たちは働くことができます
called protoplasts
プロトプラストと呼ばれる
you can go with some genes
いくつかの遺伝子を使っていける
fleeting performance
つかの間のパフォーマンス
but this one has two
しかし、これには2つあります
Your brief performance is actually
あなたの短いパフォーマンスは実際には
you may be too short the first time
初めてでは短すぎるかもしれません
You didn't grow to say a few weeks
数週間と言うほど成長しなかった
You don't get through the whole development process
開発プロセス全体を完了できない
This is a
これは
The second process of your Train Sink
トレインシンクの 2 番目のプロセス
You would put, for example, in a normal cell
たとえば、通常のセルに次のように入力します。
maybe only 100 proteins
おそらくタンパク質は 100 個だけ
You Train Sink go down
あなたは電車のシンクが落ちます
give it 10,000 protein
プロテインを10,000個与える
it is more than itself
それはそれ自体以上のものです
so you see something
それで何かが見えます
sometimes you don't know
時々あなたは知りません
It turned out to be a rather troublesome one.
かなり面倒な事になってしまった。
So we sometimes experiment
だから私たちは時々実験します
We would prefer the so-called
いわゆる
stable line
安定したライン
after turning around
振り向いた後
We're not even going to use a
を使うつもりもありません
Driving values ​​for a large number of representations
多数の表現の値を駆動する
Let this gene be expressed in large quantities
この遺伝子を大量に発現させましょう
We're going to use its own drive value instead
代わりに独自のドライブ値を使用します
what is its own driving value
それ自体の推進価値は何ですか
it at a certain time
それはある時間に
The amount of performance will be very precisely controlled
パフォーマンスの量は非常に正確に制御されます
let's take a look
見てみましょう
For example, the protein value
たとえば、タンパク質の値
silver light protein
シルバーライトプロテイン
Let's see where it behaves
どこで動作するか見てみましょう
will it help you on something
何か役に立ちますか
These we can do research on
私たちはこれらについて研究することができます
so we sometimes
だから私たちは時々
You have to be very precise to control these things
これらを制御するには非常に正確でなければなりません
is there any problem
何か問題ある
I just saw that
ちょうどそれを見ました
This little Liu is a set of black hole postcards
この小さなリューはブラックホールのポストカードのセットです
very good
とても良い
Does he know about black holes?
彼はブラックホールについて知っていますか?
it's us
それは私たちです
With this very bright spot Zhongyuanyuan
このとても明るい場所で
Cooperate with all over the world
世界中で協力する
so we must strive
だから私たちは努力しなければなりません
still a few
まだ少し
i want to ask questions
質問したいです
I want to ask
聞きたいです
that for example
それは例えば
The pollen house that the teacher said
先生が言っていた花粉の家
In this way, the seed can be produced
このようにして種を作ることができます
Matching strain
適合するひずみ
ask me like this
こうやって聞いてください
For example, our guava
たとえば、私たちのグアバ
Suppose its seed has 100 flowers
その種に100個の花があると仮定します。
like this
このような
Is it the pollen of every pollen house
どこの花粉小屋の花粉ですか？
both from the same
どちらも同じから
The other ones also come from the same flower
他のものも同じ花から来ています
it's the gold here thank you
こちらはゴールドです、ありがとう
So this thing we will
それで、これは私たちがやります
actually very similar
実際に非常によく似ています
For example, you say we
たとえば、あなたは私たちだと言います
Is it yours that can be told in another way?
別の言い方で言えるのはあなたのものですか？
Did we generate those plants with bad heads all the same?
私たちは、同じように頭の悪い植物を生成したのでしょうか?
you can ask
質問できるよ
In fact, we say that we are all the same
実際、私たちは皆同じだと言います
Our brothers and sisters unless you are a twin today
あなたが今日双子でない限り、私たちの兄弟姉妹
Otherwise, you will be different from your brothers and sisters
そうしないと、あなたは兄弟や姉妹とは違うことになります
So the same pollen house
つまり、同じ花粉ハウス
fertilization process
受精プロセス
its last so-called single back bottom
最後のいわゆるシングルバックボトム
With the single back, they will have the so-called dye combination
シングルバックでは、いわゆる染料の組み合わせになります。
when together
一緒にいるとき
This intermediate chromosome will call
この中間染色体は
many things will happen
たくさんのことが起こるだろう
So we sometimes do experiments
それで私たちは時々実験をします
will find
見つけます
You can see every pollen store
すべての花粉ストアが表示されます
The seed produced by fertilization is a single individual
受精してできた種子は一個体である
Every seed behaves differently
すべてのシードは異なる動作をします
you all look the same
あなたは皆同じに見えます
right? people all look the same
そうでしょう？人はみんな同じに見えます
everyone is different
誰もが違う
You are different from your brothers and sisters
あなたは兄弟や姉妹とは違います
you go and see
あなたは行って見ます
Every seed is like your brothers and sisters
すべての種はあなたの兄弟姉妹のようなものです
looks like seeds
種子のように見えます
But their reactions are totally different
でも彼らの反応は全く違う
So really throughout
本当にずっと
so what good is it
それで何が良いのですか
When your plant goes through what is called a chromosome
植物がいわゆる染色体を通過するとき
The pair calls for these
ペアはこれらを要求します
bullets you spawn
あなたが生み出す弾丸
there will always be one
常に1つあります
when your environment is not suitable
環境が合わないとき
Maybe under these 1000 seeds
おそらくこの 1000 個の種子の下に
have one or two
1つまたは2つ持っています
can survive
生き残ることができる
so your species
だからあなたの種族は
Only then can we continue to react
そうして初めて、私たちは反応し続けることができるのです
Like the Iron Lily we just talked about
先ほど話したアイアンリリーのように
Iron Lily Seeds
アイアンリリーの種
if i count
数えたら
A seed of an iron blast lily grown out of a flower
花から生えた鉄爆ユリの種
so quite a lot
とてもたくさん
but each made
でもそれぞれが作った
Probably not the same
おそらく同じではないでしょう
So this fun place is
さて、この楽しい場所は、
So sometimes we make mutant beads
だから時々突然変異ビーズを作るんだ
You see, this is a mutant strain of the pollen tube
ほら、これは花粉管の変異株です
you should think it's gonna die
死ぬと思ったほうがいいよ
but it's weird
でもそれは奇妙だ
I don't know I don't understand now
分からない 今は分からない
life always will
人生はいつもそうなる
will find its way out
出口を見つけるだろう
it will always have in you
それはあなたの中にいつもあるでしょう
Five or six seeds will be able to bear fruit
5～6個の種が実を結ぶでしょう
So you can keep doing time
だから時間をやり続けることができる
so fun
とても楽しいです
its not all dead
全員が死んでいるわけではない
it means you are an arab
それはあなたがアラブ人であることを意味します
Can produce fifty or sixty flowers
50～60本の花を咲かせることができる
One flower can bear fifty or sixty seeds
1つの花に50～60個の種ができる
but you are important
でもあなたは重要です
severe mutant beads
重篤な突然変異ビーズ
there are always a few seeds left
いつも種が少しだけ残っている
you can keep doing
やり続けることができます
A lot of fun
とても楽しいこと
I don't know why
どうしてか分かりません
this is what we actually
これが私たちが実際にしていることです
we always wanted
私たちはいつも望んでいた
also want to know
私も知りたいです
Why
なぜ
Thank you, excellent talk
ありがとう、素晴らしい話
i want to ask
聞きたいです
You want to talk about an iron cannon board
鉄砲台について話したいのですか
Is it native to Taiwan?
台湾原産なのでしょうか？
Is it Nectar Lili?
ネクターリリかな？
iron cannon board
鉄製の大砲ボード
I use East Lili
イーストリリ使ってます
we want to find out now
私たちは今知りたいのです
We know when there is essence
いつ本質があるのか​​を私たちは知っています
There are also medical treatments that cannot be let go
手放せない医療もある
With medical treatment and discounts
治療・割引あり
very close to lilly
非常接近利利
So if your research
したがって、あなたの研究が
You use this seed in Taiwan
台湾ではこの種を使用しています
is the seed of Taiwan
台湾の種です
or bio-decoration seeds for sale
または販売用のバイオ装飾種子
The iron cannon box we used before
以前使っていた鉄砲箱
Is East Lily
イーストリリーです
basically bought by the seed company
基本的に種子会社に買収される
But in the future we will use
しかし、将来的には使用します
What I just said will use Taiwan
私が今言ったことは台湾を利用することになります
Taiwan box
台湾ボックス
among us
私たちの中
Another No. 1 Taiwan pendulum box
もう一つの台湾No.1振り子ボックス
These are the ones I use now
これらは現在使用されています
Commercial of these East Lily
このイーストリリーのCM
It is self incompatible
それは自己互換性がありません
That is to say, my own flowers are not able to
つまり、自分の花にはできないのです。
receive flowers produce flowers
花を受け取る 花を作る
But Taiwan's display box is very special
しかし、台湾のディスプレイボックスは非常に特別です
it can
できる
So it gives us another big
それで、それは私たちに別の大きなものを与えます
yes i want to ask him
はい、彼に聞きたいです
common environment is
共通の環境は
environmental
環境
is different
異なります
OK Taiwan Lily is basically found in the mountains
OK タイワンユリは基本的に山で見られます
But we can grow in the greenhouse
でも温室でも成長できるよ
We also did Xiao Xiang here
ここでもシャオシャンをやりました
We could have done it last time too
前回もできたかもしれない
We self-pollinate to produce
私たちは自家受粉して生産します
received quite a lot of fruit
かなりたくさんの果物を受け取りました
probably too
おそらくも
it can receive hundreds no problem
何百もの問題なく受信できます
so we have been doing
それで私たちはやっています
So it's like a worm cage
つまり虫かごのようなものです
or that ginger
それともあの生姜
Its flowering is the same as Lily's
花の咲き方はユリと同じです
this chicken is the same
この鶏も同じです
sorry i really don't know that
ごめんなさい、それは本当にわかりません
OK
OK
Thanks
ありがとう
Seems like this black hole is funny
このブラックホールは面白いようです
I was asked just now
たった今質問されました
actually quite interesting
実際かなり興味深い
I would love to ask about flowering plants
草花についてお聞きしたいのですが
some are blossoming in the industry
業界で花開いている人もいます
is it possible to change
変更することは可能ですか
make it bloom by day
一日のうちに咲かせる
Of course I think this is for example
もちろんこれは例えばだと思います
You can be like our director
あなたも当社のディレクターのようになれる
What he does is related to light
彼のやっていることは光に関係している
Light can regulate flowering
光は開花を調節できる
you can make these changes
これらの変更を行うことができます
But I miss Ye Lai Xiang
でもイェ・ライシャンが恋しい
If you let it open during the day, I don’t know if it smells good or not
日中開けておくと良い香りがするかどうかはわかりませんが、
So I feel this thing
だから私はこのことを感じます
We knew you could change into one of its shapes
あなたがその形の一つに変わることができることを私たちは知っていました
but you may lose other
しかし、他のものを失う可能性があります
So I think it's a lot
だから多いと思うよ
We may need improvement as a whole
全体的に改善が必要かも知れません
is there any good for us doing this
私たちがこれをすることに何か良いことはありますか？
so i think sometimes
だから私は時々思う
But actually I think we sometimes
でも実際には時々思うよ
when we're all doing
みんなでやってるとき
We are the caretakers who discover its creation
私たちはその創造物を発見する管理人です
we are not inventing we are discovering
私たちは発明しているのではなく、発見しているのです
But its discovery must have its uses
しかし、その発見には用途があるはずです
So I can say that it should be possible to make this adjustment
したがって、この調整を行うことは可能であるはずだと言えます
Even we say they have done a lot
私たちでも、彼らは多くのことをやったと言っています
How to tune with light for flowering
開花に合わせて光を調整する方法
But this we basically understand its mechanism
しかし、これでそのメカニズムはほぼ理解できました
But I don't think it does
でも見えてないみたい
I don't know if there is such an attempt in the future to make
今後そのような試みがあるかどうかはわかりませんが、
Arab worlds bloom at night
アラブ世界は夜に花開く
but i don't know what's the use
でも何の役に立つのか分からない
if there is no problem
問題がなければ
Our black hole is about as fun as it gets.
私たちのブラックホールは、最高に楽しいものです。
So here's another
それで、ここにもう一つあります
yes
はい
study process
勉強のプロセス
I think
私が思うに
not i think
そうではないと思います
In fact, I have always liked biological things.
実は私は昔から生物的なものが好きでした。
this
これ
And then the one that really let me pluck it in
そして、本当に夢中にさせてくれたのが
I was very impressed that I was a freshman
一年生だったのでとても感動しました
i don't know what to do now
今何をすればいいのか分かりません
I'm talking about my freshman year
1年生の頃の話です
university metropolis
大学都市
We used to have bank dances when we first entered college.
私たちが大学に入学したばかりの頃はバンクダンスをしていました。
right
右
You'll probably all go to the bank dance
君たちはきっとみんなバンクダンスに行くだろう
We were also unavoidable that time
あの時も僕らは避けられなかった
Let's go to the bank dance
銀行ダンスに行きましょう
you know us
あなたは私たちを知っていますか
Country kids are always shy
田舎の子供たちはいつも恥ずかしがり屋です
I guess it's not fun
面白くないと思うよ
He and I are above the theater
彼と私は劇場の上にいる
above our own theater
私たちの劇場の上に
There is a bright classroom
明るい教室です
It turned out that a senior was doing an experiment
先輩が実験をしていたことが判明
I'll go in and talk to him
中に入って彼と話します
Senior, I'm just going to strike up a conversation anyway.
先輩、とにかく会話を始めるつもりです。
What are you doing
あなたは何をしている
After we're done talking, the dance is over.
会話が終わったらダンスは終わりです。
But from that day I knew
でも、その日からわかったのです
i want to do research
研究をしたいです
so i really didn't lie to you
だから私は本当にあなたに嘘をついていませんでした
I study hard in college
私は大学で一生懸命勉強します
everyone can
みんなが出来る
we play too, right?
私たちも遊びますよね？
but also play
でも遊びもする
but we study hard
でも私たちは一生懸命勉強します
Of course, you may be all about books
もちろん、あなたは本が大好きかもしれません
Why
なぜ
Because my senior told me
先輩に言われたから
We are also very obedient
私たちもとても従順です
The senior said you want to apply to go abroad
先輩はあなたが海外に行きたいと言いました
your grades are better
あなたの成績は良くなりました
so how about good grades
それで成績はどうですか
study
念書
so you play and play
だからあなたは遊んで遊んで
but you know what you want
でもあなたはあなたが何を望んでいるのか知っています
so i finished college
それで大学を卒業した
Then go to graduate school
その後大学院に進学
then became a soldier
それから兵士になった
After serving as a soldier
當完兵以後
because i know i'm in
私が入っていることを知っているから
I used to do it myself
以前は自分でやっていた
Comparing the traditional research on occupational science
従来の作業科学研究との比較
Don't know anything about molecular biology
分子生物学について何も知らない
i know that's a trend
それがトレンドだということは知っています
So after I finish my military service
だから兵役を終えたら
i served as a soldier at the youth headquarters
私は青年本部で兵士として勤務しました
it's very close
とても近いです
So after my young headquarters served as a soldier
それで、私の若い本部が兵士として勤務した後、
Come to Zhongying Yuan as a doppelganger
ドッペルゲンガーとして中英院に来てください
research assistant
研究助手
our same issue
私たちと同じ問題
Later, they are our current colleagues
その後、彼らは私たちの現在の同僚になりました
many
多くの
So after two years as an assistant
それでアシスタントとして2年間働いた後、
study abroad
出國念書
So I've been all the way
だから私はずっと行ってきた
thanks for the grades
成績をありがとう
everything went well
全てが上手く行きました
I'm all over this
もうこれ以上だ
environment of this study
この研究の環境
research environment
研究環境
because i just want
私はただ欲しいから
So I was in America
それで私はアメリカにいました
when you come back
あなたが戻ってくるとき
I also only apply for the position of the China Campus Institute
私もチャイナキャンパスインスティチュートのポジションのみに応募します
I didn't upgrade any other
他にはアップグレードしませんでした
also really thank god
神様にも本当に感謝しています
just came back
ちょうど今戻ったとこだよ
Then it is really a very
それから、それは本当に非常に
In the future, I hope that all young students will have the opportunity
将来的には、すべての若い学生にその機会が与えられることを願っています
You can come to our job site to have a look
私たちの求人サイトに来て見てください
These teachers are really great.
この先生方は本当に素晴らしいです。
They are many, many times stronger than me
彼らは私よりも何倍も強いです
especially those new
特に新しいものは
you can get from everyone
みんなからもらえるよ
like us
私たちのような
I just said after we got back here
ここに戻ってから言いました
we have all been
私たちは皆そうしてきました
I think education is very important
教育はとても大切だと思う
So I'm probably all except us math students
だから私たち数学の学生以外はおそらく全員
we will take students number of students
学生を受け入れます 学生の数
Our program is very good
私たちのプログラムはとても良いです
Look at these two summer students
この二人の夏の学生を見てください
the year before last year
一昨年
they last
彼らは続く
We won our last games
私たちは最後の試合に勝ちました
The two high school students I just talked about
先ほど話した二人の高校生
They got awards
彼らは賞を受賞しました
They are also participating in the National Science Fair
彼らは全国科学フェアにも参加しています
get this too
これも入手してください
so we have a lot of opportunities like this
なのでこのような機会がたくさんあります
able to attract students
生徒を惹きつけることができる
I think this is probably us
おそらくこれが私たちだと思います
high school
高校
high school i
高校の私
I also participate in the biological society
生物学会にも参加しています
The senior generation participates in clubs and other high schools
シニア世代はクラブや他の高校に参加
In the second-generation high school clubs, only the third-year students are studying
高校2期生クラブでは3年生のみが勉強しています
So I didn't do very well
だからあまりうまくいかなかった
same is
同じです
thanks for sharing
共有してくれてありがとう
you just spoke
あなたは今話しました
thank god twice
神に二度感謝します
yes
はい
so you're probably a christian
だからあなたはおそらくクリスチャンです
i think that
私はそう思います
sorry i'm a christian too
ごめんなさい、私もクリスチャンです
we in christian education we speak
私たちはキリスト教教育の中で話します
Evolution and Creation
進化と創造
in your experience
あなたの経験の中で
Who do you think is more likely to summon
誰が召喚される可能性が高いと思いますか
In fact, I think evolution
実際、私は進化だと思う
your speech
あなたのスピーチ
actually stand by me
実際に私のそばにいてください
I think the theory of evolution is
私が思う進化論は、
I mean something about you
つまり、あなたについてのことです
He can
彼はできる
probably means
おそらく意味します
giraffe neck
キリンの首
right
右
longer
より長いです
as long as in that environment
その環境にいる限り
it's getting less and less
どんどん少なくなっていきます
it's getting higher
高くなってます
But you said the giraffe was going to turn into a rhino
でも君はキリンがサイになるって言ったね
but a bit difficult
でもちょっと難しい
But the giraffe neck
でもキリンの首は
just run out
ただ足りなくなる
this means
これの意味は
Come to agree. From this point of view, I agree.
この観点からは、私も同意します。
creation theory
創造論
If there is a word, it is impossible for you to be more difficult
言葉があれば、これ以上難しいことはありません
I have no idea
何も思いつきません
I think
私が思うに
We are so complicated now alone
私たちは今一人でとても複雑です
You said you want to start with the original one
オリジナルから始めたいって言ってたよね
maybe tens of thousands of years
おそらく何万年も
I think it's a little difficult
少し難しいと思います
I find it difficult
それは難しいと思います
I think it's almost time
そろそろ時間だと思う
Our other postcards must be given to Mr. Zhao
私たちの他のポストカードは趙さんに渡さなければなりません
good
良い
I'm just curious, that's what
ただ興味があるだけです、そういうことです
in that
その中で
Infertility
自交不清合
Can
できる
infertile hybrid
不妊ハイブリッド
And that self-pollinating hand
そしてその自家受粉の手
In the process of pollen hall formation
花粉ホールの形成過程
What would be the difference in those lead substances
それらの鉛物質の違いは何でしょうか
OK
OK
Self-incompatibility of Baozi body
包子体の自己不和合性
is the so-called
いわゆる
Because the so-called incompatible thing
いわゆる相性の悪いものだから
on the surface of pollen grains
花粉粒の表面に
The surface of the pollen grain is from
花粉粒の表面は、
So-called
所謂的
flowers are coming
花が来ています
So the one where the flower will come is a diploid
つまり、花から出たものは二倍体です
So it's bun body
ということでバンボディです
The gametophyte is indistinct
配偶体は不明瞭です
When the pollen house the gamete grows in the pistil
花粉が家にあるとき、配偶子は雌しべの中で成長します
Inside, this is the configuration body
内部は、これが構成本体です
what about this time
今回はどうですか
From its suffix, it will be clear that it is called SRNS
接尾辞から、SRNS と呼ばれていることがわかります。
This goes into the pollen tube of the plant
これが植物の花粉管に入ります
This SRNS will put the Mission-9NS inside
この SRNS には Mission-9NS が組み込まれます。
so7RNA
so7RNA
All of these RNAs are kneeled down
これらのRNAはすべてひざまずいている
So it has no way to cause
だからそれを引き起こす方法はありません
Another one is the so-called
もう一つは、いわゆる、
Jia Riko
賈里子
Not Kelson
ケルソンではありません
some have one another
お互いに持っている人もいます
in the so-called self-infertility
いわゆる自己不妊症で
Also the pollen tubes are on the inside
花粉管も内側にある
but it caused
しかしそれが引き起こした
No, this is Jia Lizi
いいえ、これは賈李子です
That lid makes it impossible to get in
その蓋があると中に入ることができなくなります
so the whole later
それで全体は後で
The entire pollen tube cannot grow
花粉管全体が成長できない
So the mechanism is slightly different
なので仕組みが少し違います
OK, I'll just NAS
OK、NAS にします
The next trial
次の裁判
December 17th
12月17日
Hu Shi
胡思
We have a lecture by Dean Gu
Dean Gu氏による講義があります
It is a popular science lecture given by President Gu of Hu Shi
胡氏の顧​​総統による人気科学講座です。
that's from the Institute of History and
それは歴史研究所からのもので、
Lecture by Wang Hongtai Research Institute
王紅台研究所による講演
From Ximenqing to Jiabaoying
西門慶から嘉宝営まで
Feminist Review and Emotional Evolution with the People of the Ming and Qing Dynasties
フェミニストの見直しと明・清時代の人々の感情的進化
very different subject
まったく異なる主題
These grids are for everyone to participate in
これらのグリッドは誰でも参加できます
next science talk
次の科学の話
Well, we thank Dr. Gao Guangyu, Gao Guang Researcher
Gao Guang研究員のGao Guangyu博士に感謝します。
"Female Reviews and Emotional Actors in the Ming and Qing Dynasties"
「明・清時代の女性評伝と情緒的俳優」